train wig ride
trainかつらの乗り隨が
Academia Sinica's August knowledge test lecture begins
中央研究院8月知識検定講座開始
We ask Vice President Liu Dong to host for us
劉東副総統に司会をお願いします
It is an honor and a pleasure to introduce the multi-institute Institute of Biomedical Sciences
複数の機関からなる生物医科学研究所をご紹介できることを大変光栄に思います。
Also my colleague Tao Minghua researcher
私の同僚の陶明華研究員でもあります
Dr. Tao graduated from the first-level department of National Taiwan University
タオ博士は国立台湾大学の第一級学部を卒業しました。
He went to study in America
彼はアメリカに留学しました
Bea University at the Top Individual
個人トップのビー大学
Get a Ph.D. in Immunology and Microbiology
免疫学と微生物学の博士号を取得する
Then he went to another top university
その後、彼は別の一流大学に進学しました
Postdoctoral Research at Stanford University in California
カリフォルニアのスタンフォード大学で博士研究員
where the main research is related to the total flow
主な研究が全体の流れに関連している場合
After that, he returned to Taiwan to enter the Academia Sinica
その後、台湾に戻り中央研究院に入学。
From assistant researcher to associate researcher to researcher very smoothly
研究助手から准研究員、研究員への移行が非常にスムーズ
Now a researcher at the Institute of Biomedical Sciences
現在、生命医科学研究所の研究員
His research work has always been related to total flow
彼の研究活動は常にトータルフローに関連しています
This year is gene therapy or immunotherapy
今年は遺伝子治療または免疫療法です
It's also his topic today
それは今日の彼の話題でもある
In this regard, he has made many contacts and contributions.
この点で、彼は多くの人脈と貢献をしてきました。
also published in good journals
良い雑誌にも掲載されています
He also received many awards
数々の賞も受賞している
including hospital
病院も含めて
Here are the many awards for young scholars
若手研究者に対する数々の賞をご紹介します
and the Ministry of Science and Technology
および科学技術省
Contact Research Award
連絡先研究賞
Immunotherapy has been
免疫療法が行われてきました
Attention in Oncology World
腫瘍学の世界で注目
Some breakthroughs in recent years
近年のいくつかの画期的な進歩
And it's a very exciting breakthrough
そしてそれは非常にエキサイティングな進歩です
In fact I was about a year ago
実は私も1年ほど前に
I also give a talk on immuno-oncology
腫瘍免疫学についても講演します
immune therapy
免疫療法
I recognize the title after
認識したらタイトルは
Immunotherapy sees light
免疫療法建署光
But in fact it's not just sign light
でも実はただのサインライトではないんです
It should be fairly obvious by now
もうそれはかなり明白になっているはずです
Very excited, Dr. Tao has his expertise in this area and the results of his research
非常に興奮しています。タオ博士はこの分野の専門知識と研究結果を持っています。
So I believe he will give us a very incisive and wonderful speech today
今日は彼がとても鋭くて素晴らしいスピーチをしてくれると信じています
We welcome Dr. Tao with warm applause
田尾先生を温かい拍手でお迎えいたします
Hello everyone Man An
みなさん、マンアンさん、こんにちは
Today is more tense than in the international lecture hall
今日は国際講堂よりも緊張しています
Because in Chinese, the task we received was to put all the slides in Chinese
中国語で、私たちが受けたタスクはすべてのスライドを中国語で作成することだったので、
Then the speeches all use Chinese nouns
それからスピーチはすべて中国語の名詞を使用します
This is a big challenge for our researchers at Academia Sinica
これは中央研究院の研究者にとって大きな課題です。
So actually these slides for this talk took quite a while to make
実際、この講演用のスライドは作成するのにかなり時間がかかりました
I hope to be able to use some relatively easy-to-understand scientific language
比較的わかりやすい科学用語を使えるようになりたいです
then communicate with everyone
それからみんなとコミュニケーションを取る
Currently this rather promising approach to cancer treatment
現在のところ、このかなり有望ながん治療アプローチ
Then I will try to introduce to you today what is immunotherapy
それでは今日は免疫療法とは何かについてご紹介したいと思います
In fact, immunotherapy
実は免疫療法って
Or our simplest is this
または、最も単純なのはこれです
Does everyone in English understand this?
英語圏の皆さんはこれを理解できますか?
using the body to fight cancer
体を使ってがんと闘う
with your own body
自分の体で
to fight cancer
がんと闘うために
In fact, against these tumors against cancer
実際、これらの腫瘍に対して、癌に対して
These key weapons are needed
これらの重要な武器が必要です
we all have
私たちは皆持っています
just because of different genetic background
遺伝的背景が違うだけで
some people his immune system
一部の人は彼の免疫システムを
Easier and more effective against cancer
がんに対してより簡単かつ効果的
some people are worse
もっと悪い人もいます
Now in immunotherapy
現在免疫療法中
I just hope to use some foreign medicine
外国の薬を使いたいと思っています
Overcome stimulates the patient's immune system
克服は患者の免疫システムを刺激します
to fight cancer
がんと闘うために
This is Cancer Immunotherapy
これががん免疫療法です
has been going on for quite a long time
かなり長い間続いています
Then I will start today
それでは今日から始めます
Because we are in a hurry
私たちは急いでいるから
I will learn from his past
彼の過去から学びます
In fact, there have been more than 100 years of research history in the past
実は100年以上の研究の歴史があり、
The current situation is what Vice President Liu just said
現状は劉副大統領が今言った通りだ
Most recently this has been around since 2010
最近では 2010 年から行われています
a big breakthrough of
大きな進歩
Also see very good prospects in patients
患者の将来性も非常に良好であることがわかります
but only just started
でもまだ始まったばかりです
the future means
未来が意味するもの
how do we go from here
ここからどうやって行くか
Can have a bigger breakthrough
より大きな突破口が開ける可能性がある
can bring more patients
より多くの患者を連れてくることができる
Then this is the mission of our Academia Sinica Research Institute
それが私たち中央研究院の使命です
Because we're not on the front lines caring for clinical patients
私たちは臨床患者のケアを最前線で行っているわけではないので、
This is the job of the clinician
これは臨床医の仕事です
But all we have to do is
しかし、私たちがしなければならないのは、
How can medical
医療はどうすればできるのか
Problems that have not yet been resolved
まだ解決されていない問題
These results can then be
これらの結果は次のようになります。
Transfer to clinic for treatment
治療のためにクリニックに搬送
Then this is the expectation of our Academia Sinica
これが私たちの中央研究院の期待です
It is also our responsibility now
それは今では私たちの責任でもあります
then i will today
それなら今日行きます
From here, the more detailed content
ここからは詳しい内容です
Actually, last month, our weekly report in Zhongyuan Hospital
実は先月、中原病院の週次報告書が発表されました。
I also wrote on the same topic, and also wrote all his Chinese
私も同じテーマで書き、彼の中国語もすべて書きました。
And I found a colleague, he is an editor, so he can understand
そして同僚を見つけました、彼は編集者なので理解できます
So I believe it will be easier for everyone to understand
なので、誰でも理解しやすいと思います
What about everyone, there will be some lectures on the sidelines, and it will be on the Internet
皆さんはどうですか、副業でいくつかの講義があり、それはインターネット上で行われます
You can also extract his PDF file
彼の PDF ファイルを抽出することもできます
Then my entire speech today will probably focus on this content.
それでは、今日の私のスピーチ全体はおそらくこの内容に焦点を当てたものになるでしょう。
Plus some new developments
さらにいくつかの新しい展開
Then, let yourself vent first, lest you get too late
それから、手遅れにならないように、まず自分の気持ちを吐き出してください
So in our lab, today I'm going to have a short, last short
それで、私たちの研究室では、今日は短い、最後の短い話をするつもりです
Let’s talk about our voice first, then the results, which is the Zhongyuan Hospital just mentioned
まず私たちの声について話しましょう。次に結果について話しましょう。それが先ほど言及した中原病院です。
That is, we need to make some breakthroughs on the basis of existing
つまり、既存の基盤に基づいていくつかのブレークスルーを行う必要があります。
Let's use some animal models to see
いくつかの動物モデルを使って見てみましょう
Uh, how can immunotherapy go a step further, uh, to improve the effect of lung transformation?
免疫療法をさらに一歩進めて、肺の変化の効果を改善するにはどうすればよいでしょうか?
Then this is my postdoctoral researcher Dr. Jiaren Wu
それから、こちらは私の博士研究員、Jiaren Wu 博士です。
And the lab assistant, uh
そして研究室助手は
He used to be National Taiwan University, uh, Vincent & Associates
彼は以前は国立台湾大学、ええと、ヴィンセント&アソシエイツに所属していました。
Graduating master's students
修士課程を卒業する学生
Yes, Cai Yiting
はい、蔡一廷
oh their work
ああ、彼らの仕事だ
What about the other thing? Today’s slides are all in Chinese.
もう 1 つはどうでしょうか? 今日のスライドはすべて中国語です。
that includes some animation
いくつかのアニメーションが含まれています
Then invite us to this one
それなら私たちをこれに招待してください
Mr. Zhang Fengbi from the art room, Mr. Zhang Zimin, assisted
美術室のZhang Fengbi氏、Zhang Zimin氏が協力しました。
come on make these slides
さあ、これらのスライドを作ってください
ok first sentence
オーケー、最初の文
This may scare many people
これは多くの人を怖がらせるかもしれません
Everyone has cancer cells in their bodies, including the current
現在のがん細胞も含め、誰もが体内にがん細胞を持っています。
In fact, of course I can't say so, uh, sure
実際には、もちろんそうは言えません、確かに
But from the evidence of many animal experiments, I will show you the evidence later
しかし、多くの動物実験の証拠から、後でその証拠をお見せします
Maybe we all have cancer cells in our bodies
もしかしたら私たちの体内には癌細胞が存在するかもしれません
good
良い
So why are most of us still cancer-free?
では、なぜ私たちのほとんどはガンに罹患していないのでしょうか?
that's because we
それは私たちだからです
no immune system
免疫システムがない
help you in
あなたを助けてください
overcome
克服
against these cancer cells
これらのがん細胞に対して
then let me first introduce
それではまず紹介させてください
Cancers that are common in Taiwan and the world
台湾と世界に多いがん
this is 104 years
今年は104年目です
Cancer Ranking in Taiwan
台湾のがんランキング
In fact, almost none of these have changed.
実際、これらはほとんど変わっていません。
Lung cancer in the first three years
最初の3年間の肺がん
Liver cancer Muscle intestine Spinal bowel
肝臓がん 筋腸 脊髄腸
Fatty bowel, liver cancer, colorectal cancer
脂肪腸、肝臓がん、大腸がん
Look at the world ranking
世界ランキングを見てみよう
he
他
The top few are lung cancer, brain cancer and colorectal cancer
上位数位は肺がん、脳腫瘍、結腸直腸がんです
So your brain cancer ranks fourth in Taiwan
あなたの脳腫瘍は台湾で4位にランクされるということですね
But it is second in the world
でも世界では2番目だよ
highest death rate
最も高い死亡率
The highest death rate is lung cancer
死亡率が最も高いのは肺がん
Then came liver cancer, then colon cancer
次に肝臓がん、そして大腸がんと続きました
So this is our common
これが私たちの共通点です
Right now it's been going on for 20+ years
現在でも20年以上続いている
Cancer is the first of the top ten experiments
がんはトップ 10 の実験の最初にランクイン
So the shape of human disease will actually change
つまり、人間の病気の形は実際に変化するでしょう
related to our medical technology
当社の医療技術に関わるもの
I'll show you guys later
後で皆さんにお見せします
is how medical technology
医療技術はどうなっているのか
How to change the shape of our disease
病気の形をどう変えるか
Now everyone is most afraid of cancer
今、誰もが最も恐れているのはガンです
but 50 years ago
でも50年前
Everyone is most afraid that it is not cancer
誰もが一番恐れているのは、がんではないということです
is another disease
別の病気です
many infectious diseases
多くの感染症
Another point is the treatment of cancer
もう一つのポイントは、がんの治療です。
The most effective cancer treatment available now
現在利用できる最も効果的ながん治療法
should be detected early
早期に発見されるべきである
if you catch cancer early
早期にがんに気づいたら
no matter what treatment
どのような治療であっても
its cure rate
その治癒率
are very high
都非常的高
For example, take this example
たとえば、この例を見てみましょう
this colorectal cancer
この大腸がんは
colorectal cancer
大腸癌
colorectal cancer in this place
こんなところに大腸がんがある
Original colorectal cancer
もともとの大腸がん
when you find out
わかったとき
If it belongs to the early
それが初期のものであれば
Doctors have many ways to control
医師にはコントロールするためのさまざまな方法がある
Surgical disaster was probably the first
外科的災害はおそらく最初だった
In addition, you can use local radiation therapy
さらに、局所放射線による治療も可能です
But if this IC package spreads
でもこのICパッケージが普及したら
Diffusion is about leaving this original position
拡散とは、この元の位置から離れることです
Transfer to Hall 08 Vascular
ホール 08 血管へ移動
For example, in this case it will go through this dry portal vein
たとえば、この場合、この乾いた門脈を通過します。
The dry portal vein is where our intestines
乾いた門脈は私たちの腸の場所です
a very important source of blood supply
非常に重要な血液供給源
With this dry portal vein
この乾いた門脈で
The IC package will spread to the first station
ICパッケージは初の駅まで普及する
just do it
早くやれよ
Many colorectal cancer patients
大腸がん患者が多い
may exceed 50%
50%を超える可能性があります
after diagnosis
診断後
dry transfer
ドライ転写
25%
２５％
Another 45% were found to have dry metastases after treatment
さらに45%は治療後に乾性転移があることが判明した
So if we can detect early
それで早期発見できれば
before dry transfer
ドライ転写前
able to treat patients of this size
この規模の患者を治療できる
Colorectal cancer has a very high cure rate
大腸がんは治癒率が非常に高い
What's more
そのうえ
This is it
これだよ
metastatic cancer
転移性がん
In fact, it is the biggest difficulty in our treatment.
実は、それが私たちの治療の最大の難関なのです。
Once the cancer has metastasized
がんが転移してしまうと
In fact, we have very few weapons at our disposal.
実際、私たちが自由に使える武器はほとんどありません。
chemotherapy
化学療法
Still the first-line drug
まだ第一選択薬
additional targeted therapy
追加の標的療法
But these are very difficult
しかし、これらはとても難しいのです
completely cured
完全に治った
The patient with metastatic cancer
転移性がんの患者さん
Immunotherapy until now
これまでの免疫療法
start to see
見え始める
seems to be ok
大丈夫のようです
it can be cured
それは治すことができます
Metastatic cancer in the past
過去に転移性がんがある
You rarely use a term like cure
治療のような言葉はめったに使いません
Most of the past
過去のほとんど
years of survival
生存年数
one year survival rate
1年生存率
three-year survival rate
3年生存率
five-year survival rate
5年生存率
rarely cured
まれに治る
so now we can start talking slowly
だから今からゆっくり話しましょう
It seems that some patients
患者さんもいるそうですよ
seems to be cured
治ったようです
But since I haven't observed long enough
でも、あまり長く観察していないので、
So it takes experience
だから経験が必要なんだよ
But from the current data
しかし、現在のデータから判断すると、
Looking at these data, it looks like he is very rich, very rich
これらのデータを見ると、彼は非常に裕福であるように見えます、非常に裕福です
that this
これは
The research is published in very top journals called Nature journals
この研究は、Nature ジャーナルと呼ばれる超一流のジャーナルに掲載されています。
You may have heard
聞いたことがあるかもしれません
That's actually this
それは実際にこれです
It turns out that I like to use it as a reference
リファレンスとして使用するのが好きであることがわかりました
to prove that it is possible that every normal human body
すべての正常な人体が可能であることを証明するために
may be cancerous
癌性の可能性がある
That's how he does it, he does this experiment
それが彼のやり方です、彼はこの実験をします
signature
導署
Then inject some chemical natural substances into this experimental department
次に、この実験部門に化学天然物質を注入します。
It seems that we usually come into contact with some natural substances
私たちは普段、何らかの自然物に触れているようです。
You eat the sun that shines inside our environment
あなたは私たちの環境の中で輝く太陽を食べる
Some natural substances exist, so we have been exposed to
いくつかの天然物質が存在するため、私たちは暴露されています。
Then this experiment he found
そこで彼が見つけたこの実験は
He injected these natural substances, a few mice
彼はこれらの天然物質を数匹のマウスに注射しました
a tumor
腫瘍
then he knocks him out
それから彼は彼をノックアウトします
What he really wants to ask is, and
彼が本当に聞きたいのは、そして
what about most mice
ほとんどのマウスはどうですか
after two hundred days
二百日後
looks healthy
健康そうに見える
so he asked a few questions
それで彼はいくつか質問しました
First, these contacts
まず、これらの連絡先
Rats exposed to chemicals from tap water 200 days ago
200日前に水道水からの化学物質にさらされたネズミ
inside his body
彼の体の中に
Are there cancer cells?
がん細胞はあるのでしょうか？
This is the first question
これが最初の質問です
The second question is
2番目の質問は、
if he
もし彼が
These mice have cancer cells in them
これらのマウスには癌細胞が存在します
why doesn't he grow into a cancer
なぜ彼は癌にならないのか
Why does it still look healthy
なぜまだ健康そうに見えるのですか
The third question is
3つ目の質問は、
Is that because of the protection provided by the immune system in these mice
それはこれらのマウスの免疫系による防御のためでしょうか
So he aimed at this experiment to answer these questions
そこで彼はこれらの質問に答えるためにこの実験を目指しました
His method is very simple
彼の方法はとてもシンプルです
Because in the laboratory where we do immunization
なぜなら、私たちが予防接種を行っている研究室では
have some tools
いくつかの道具を持っています
We can regulate, control our immune system
私たちは免疫システムを調節し、制御することができます
For example
例えば
For example this, if
たとえばこれの場合、
The immune system provides protection
免疫システムは保護を提供します
Then if we destroy the immunity of this mouse
このマウスの免疫を破壊すると
So if the mouse has cancer cells
つまり、マウスに癌細胞がある場合、
Will it grow out then?
それで伸びるでしょうか？
So logically it should be easy to understand
論理的には理解しやすいはずです
So that's really how it works
それが実際の仕組みです
It can use some antibody drugs
一部の抗体医薬を使用できる
different types of immune cells
さまざまな種類の免疫細胞
clear up destroy
一掃する 破壊する
it turns out that
それは判明しました
If you destroy the immune cells of the mice
マウスの免疫細胞を破壊すると
especially cell
特に細胞
this is us tonight
これが今夜の私たちです
The most important protagonist of all is to lift the cells
すべての中で最も重要な主役は細胞を持ち上げることです
it found that fifty percent of the mice
その結果、マウスの50パーセントが
You see it's here two hundred days later
二百日後にここにあるのがわかるだろう
It puts this antibody drug in
この抗体医薬を入れます
destroy our immune cells
私たちの免疫細胞を破壊する
As a result, once it destroys the cell
その結果、一度細胞を破壊すると、
You can see that more than half of the mice grow out of their seeds
半分以上のネズミが種から成長していることがわかります。
So this experiment clearly proves that
したがって、この実験は明らかに次のことを証明しています
In mice that had been exposed to chemicals
化学物質に曝露されたマウスでは
must have cancer cells
癌細胞があるに違いない
It's just the mouse's immune system
それはまさにマウスの免疫システムです
Especially the protection provided by kick cells
特にキックセルによって提供される保護
So although it has cancer cells, it can coexist peacefully with it
つまり、がん細胞があっても、それと平和に共存できるのです。
It's fine if it doesn't grow cancer
癌にならなければ良いのですが
so think about it
だからそれについて考えてください
That means we can be exposed to chemicals that may be more
つまり、私たちはさらに多くの化学物質にさらされる可能性があります。
chemical source may be more
化学源がもっとあるかもしれない
We have native objects in the environment
環境内にネイティブ オブジェクトがあります
There are chemical origins and physical origins
化学的起源と物理的起源がある
There are also some viruses that come from
由来するウイルスもあります
But most of us are actually pretty healthy.
しかし、私たちのほとんどは実際にはかなり健康です。
He has to thank our immune system
彼は私たちの免疫システムに感謝しなければなりません
Do we really have cancer cells in our body?
私たちの体内には本当にがん細胞が存在するのでしょうか？
It's actually hard to judge
実は判断が難しい
This may depend on our most sophisticated
これは私たちの最も洗練されたものに依存する可能性があります
Cancer cell detection system
がん細胞検出システム
Well, now it’s probably CT, this kind of computerized tomography
まあ、今はおそらくCT、この種のコンピューター断層撮影でしょう
The computerized tomography scan, we all know its sensitivity
コンピューター断層撮影スキャン、その感度は誰もが知っています
If it is about 0.3 cm to 0.5 cm, it is difficult to confirm
0.3cm～0.5cm程度だと確認が難しい
a little bit, the size of a grain of rice
ほんの少し、米粒くらいの大きさ
But everyone knows this, how many cancer cells are there in a tumor of this size
しかし、これは誰もが知っていることですが、このサイズの腫瘍にはどれくらいの数の癌細胞が存在しますか
Hundreds of millions, that is to say, the sensitivity of our current detection
数億、つまり現在の検出感度
For example, below 0.3 cm, it is actually difficult for us to detect this kind of
たとえば、0.3cm以下では、この種の物質を検出することは実際には困難です。
But there are already very, very many cancer cells in it.
しかし、その中にはすでに非常に多くのがん細胞が存在しています。
Fortunately, most of the immune types are healthy.
幸いなことに、ほとんどの免疫タイプは健康です。
The other thing is that we have to take care of our immune system
もう一つは、私たちは免疫システムに気を配らなければならないということです
Then let it work normally
あとは普通に動作させましょう
So maintaining a healthy lifestyle has become very important
したがって、健康的なライフスタイルを維持することが非常に重要になっています
Next, I will talk about immunotherapy from the beginning.
次に、免疫療法について最初からお話します。
The Past of Cancer Immunotherapy
がん免疫療法の過去
This is about a very young doctor at that time.
これは当時の非常に若い医師の話です。
Called Dr. Corley
コーリー博士と呼ばれる
This Dr. Corley was around the end of the 19th century
このコーリー博士は19世紀末頃の人物です。
he is a surgeon
彼は外科医です
At that time there was only one treatment for cancer
当時、がんの治療法は一つしかありませんでした
It's surgery
手術だよ
Traditional Therapeutic Radiation Today
現在の伝統的な治療用放射線
Madam Juju hadn't discovered
マダム・ジュジュは発見していなかった
chemotherapy not yet
化学療法はまだです
Don't put off treatment later
治療を後回しにしないでください
The only thing is to cut
カットするだけです
Dr. Corley found
コーリー博士が見つけた
he observed clinically
彼は臨床的に観察した
In fact, many of our medical advances are like this
実際、私たちの医学の進歩の多くはこれに似ています
Just start from observation
まずは観察から始めましょう
then you will be curious
そうすればあなたは興味を持つでしょう
Curiosity triggers your research motivation
好奇心が研究のモチベーションを高める
he found out
彼は見つけた
He found a patient in Fresh Stand
彼はフレッシュスタンドで患者を見つけた
With his surgeon expertise, he thinks this patient probably won't live long.
外科医の専門知識を踏まえると、この患者はおそらく長くは生きられないと彼は考えている。
However, this patient developed a bacterial infection during hospitalization.
しかし、この患者は入院中に細菌感染症を発症しました。
He thought at that time, there were no antibiotics for humans
彼は当時、人間用の抗生物質は存在しないと考えていました。
Bacterial infection is very serious
細菌感染は非常に深刻です
Then some patients may not make it through, and some patients may survive.
そうすれば、一部の患者は助からないかもしれないし、一部の患者は生き残るかもしれない。
He discovered this Fresh Dan bacterial infection, repeated bacterial infections
彼はこのフレッシュダンの細菌感染症を発見し、細菌感染症を繰り返しました
But it is strange that after his bacterial infection is cured, he always disappears
しかし、細菌感染が治った後はいつも姿を消してしまうのは不思議です
So this was a big shock to him.
ですから、これは彼にとって大きなショックでした。
Because for his profession, the cancer he judged is already a terminal cancer patient.
なぜなら、彼の職業上、彼が判断したガンはすでに末期ガン患者だからだ。
how can it be good
どうすれば良いでしょうか
So he put forward a hypothesis
そこで彼はある仮説を立てた
In fact, you see, our science is all about observation, making hypotheses, and making bold assumptions.
実際、私たちの科学は観察、仮説、そして大胆な仮定がすべてです。
Be careful next time
次回からは気をつけてね
Then he did it and came up with a hypothesis. He thought maybe it was a bacterial infection and it was cured.
そこで彼は仮説を立て、これは細菌感染症ではないかと考え、それが治ったのです。
This Freshden's cancer
このフレッシュデンがん
Then he went back to find their hospital
それから彼は病院を探しに戻りました
this new york cancer hospital
このニューヨークのがん病院
Is there a similar case
同様のケースはありますか
As a result, he found more than 30 similar cases
その結果、同様のケースを30件以上発見した
Bacterial infection occurs
細菌感染が起こる
As a result, almost half of the cancer disappeared
その結果、がんの半分近くが消失しました。
So this caused him to be more active
これにより彼はより活発になりました
So he started to execute the first
それで彼は最初のことを実行し始めました
looks dangerous now
今は危険に見える
a so-called human experiment
いわゆる人体実験
He finds the next patient to see him
彼は次に診​​てくれる患者を見つける
Called Signal Zola
シグナル・ゾラと呼ばれる
Everyone look at this, he has a photo to keep
みんなこれを見て、彼は保存しておきたい写真を持っているよ
have invested in
に投資しました
Then it has metastasized to the lungs and variable glands
その後、肺と可変腺に転移しました
This patient probably won't live long.
この患者はおそらく長くは生きられないだろう。
Then this case will carry out his clinical trial
その後、この患者は臨床試験を実施することになる
Bacteria
細菌
injected into his tumor
彼の腫瘍に注射された
In the end, I called once, twice, three times, but it didn't seem to work.
結局、1回、2回、3回と電話しましたが、ダメだったようです。
He also does not cause infection
彼は感染症を引き起こすこともありません
Of course the tumor is fine
もちろん腫瘍は大丈夫です
Then he wondered if his bacteria wasn't doing well
それから彼は、自分の細菌の調子が良くないのではないかと疑問に思いました。
So I found this one
それで私はこれを見つけました
Those who have attended junior high school, high school, or religious studies
中学、高校、宗教科に通っていた方
This is the famous Koho
これが有名な香峰です。
father of bacteriology
細菌学の父
He's the one who came up with the Koho collimator
彼はKohoコリメータを考え出した人です
german science prize
ドイツ科学賞
just go ask him
彼に聞いてみてください
because he invented a way to grow bacteria
彼は細菌を増殖させる方法を発明したからです
So you get the purest, most powerful bacteria
したがって、最も純粋で最も強力な細菌が得られます
As a result, after he injected the bacteria
その結果、細菌を注射した後、
Sure enough, it caused a serious bacterial infection.
案の定、重篤な細菌感染症を引き起こしました。
chills, nausea, vomiting, fever
悪寒、吐き気、嘔吐、発熱
This isolated symptom occurs
この孤立した症状が発生する
This is a serious bacterial infection
これは重篤な細菌感染症です
if found
見つかったら
Symptoms of this bacterial infection
この細菌感染症の症状
What did you find?
あなたは何を見つけましたか？
This patient has cancer in his head
この患者は頭に癌を患っています
It disappeared completely within two weeks.
2週間以内に完全に消えました。
Cancer is also under control
がんもコントロールできています
Then the patient will be discharged
その後、患者は退院します
This was supposed to last a few weeks
これは数週間続くはずだった
eight more years
あと8年
But then his cancer came back
しかしその後、彼の癌が再発した
But these eight years are earned
でもこの8年間は稼いだものだ
The healthy ones lived for eight years
健康な人は8年生きた
What about Koho?
コーホはどうですか？
the collie
コリー
he invented
彼が発明した
He thought he was doing the right thing
彼は自分が正しいことをしていると思っていた
for treatment
治療のために
Therefore, during his decades as a criminal doctor
したがって、犯罪医師としての彼の数十年の間に、
He published about 1500 cases
彼は約1500件の症例を発表した
he has 500 cases
彼は500件のケースを持っています
is effective for cancer
ガンに効果がある
is one third
3分の1です
This is actually from the current point of view
これは実際には現在の視点からのものです
It is also an unlikely figure
これもありえない数字です
but it's a pity to say
でも言うのは残念だ
At that time, everyone didn't know about immunology
当時は免疫学なんて誰も知らなかった
no basis in immunology
免疫学には根拠がない
don't know how it works
仕組みがわかりません
Its biggest problem is that it can do it well and others can't do it
その最大の問題は、自分はうまくできるが、他の人はそれができないことです
other people's consciousness can't do it
他人の意識ではそれができない
for any medical action
あらゆる医療行為に対して
The method of medical treatment must be repeated
治療方法を繰り返す必要がある
That is to say, I did it at National Taiwan University.
つまり、台湾大学でやりました。
It should be done in City University
市大でやればいいのに
Otherwise, if you only rely on some individual reports
それ以外の場合、一部の個別レポートのみに依存する場合
The absence of recurrence does not actually constitute an effective medical
再発がないことは実際には効果的な医療とは言えません
So this is what we need to do clinical trials
これが臨床試験を行う必要があるということです
Different levels of clinical trials are a big reason
臨床試験のレベルの違いが大きな理由
So an early result of this Coly like this
この Coly の初期の結果は次のとおりです
have received little attention from the medical profession.
医療専門家からはほとんど注目されていません。
Slowly, after a few years
ゆっくりと、数年経ってから
Mrs. Gilly found Ray
ジリー夫人がレイを見つけた
then start
それから始めます
Even entered the era of Radiation radiation therapy
放射線治療の時代にも突入
Then around 1940
それから1940年頃
Discovery of chemical drug that kills cancer cells
がん細胞を殺す化学薬品を発見
entered the era of chemotherapy
化学療法の時代に突入した
then around 2000
それから2000年頃
It was found that cancer cells have mutations in some genes than normal cells
がん細胞は正常細胞に比べて一部の遺伝子に変異があることが判明
That can use some drugs to control these mutant receptors
これらの変異受容体を制御するためにいくつかの薬物を使用できる可能性がある
This is called targeted therapy
これは標的療法と呼ばれます
it's listed here
ここにリストされています
Surgery Radiotherapy Chemotherapy Targeted Therapy
手術 放射線療法 化学療法 標的療法
Then this constitutes the mainstream of cancer treatment now.
そして、これが現在のがん治療の主流となっています。
Immunotherapy has been only in academia
免疫療法は学界のみで行われている
And even in academia people don't quite believe
そして学界でも人々はあまり信じていない
until recently
最近まで
These are the developments that I want to introduce to you after today.
以上が今日以降の展開についてご紹介したいと思います。
good
良い
Alright, the next thing I want to do is to introduce to you
さて、次にご紹介したいのは、
the body's immune system
体の免疫システム
The immune system is not actually developed to treat cancer
免疫システムは実際には癌を治療するために発達していません
Because of our surrounding environment
私たちの周囲の環境のせいで
There have always been a lot of vitamins
昔からビタミンが豊富だった
Everyone is protected by the immune system without realizing it.
誰もが知らず知らずのうちに免疫システムによって守られています。
you don't know how precious it is
それがどれほど貴重なことかあなたは知りません
because everyone looks healthy
みんな健康そうに見えるから
But you need to know the importance of the immune system to health
しかし、健康に対する免疫システムの重要性を知る必要があります
it's actually really easy
実はとても簡単です
You can know it from immunocompromised patients
免疫不全患者からそれを知ることができます
If the patient
もし患者が
Whether congenital or acquired
先天的か後天的か
lack of immune system
免疫システムの欠如
He can't survive under normal circumstances
彼は通常の状況では生きていけない
Like a famous example called Bobble Child
ボブルチャイルドという有名な例のように
His innate immune switch
彼の自然免疫スイッチ
He lives in a segregated village
彼は隔離された村に住んでいます
and then all the activities
それからすべてのアクティビティ
must be performed in a sterile environment
無菌環境で実施する必要がある
Generally speaking, it is normal for us
一般的に言えば、私たちにとってはそれが普通です
These dimensional creatures are not at all a problem
この次元の生き物は全く問題ない
Probably well known to him
おそらく彼にはよく知られている
The immune system is actually helping us deal with all these creatures
免疫システムは実際、これらすべての生き物に対処するのに役立っています
This is innate, each of us has
これは生まれつきのものであり、私たち一人一人が持っています
We just need to learn now
今すぐ学ばなければなりません
How to apply it and train it
それをどのように応用してトレーニングするか
Let it help us fight the disease
病気に抵抗するのに役立ちますように
But the immune system is actually doing two things at once
しかし、免疫システムは実際には 2 つのことを同時に行っています
it should have heard font immune disease
フォント免疫疾患を聞くべきだった
If immune hyperactivation
免疫力が亢進している場合
or it was supposed to attack dimensional creatures
あるいは次元の生き物を攻撃するはずだった
If it turns out to attack your own cells,
自分自身の細胞を攻撃することが判明した場合、
that's an autoimmune disease
それは自己免疫疾患です
Font immune disease is actually very difficult to treat
フォント免疫疾患は実際には治療が非常に困難です
related to genetics
遺伝に関係する
So how to control the immune system
では、免疫システムを制御するにはどうすればよいでしょうか
Make it able to deal with alien invading dimensional creatures
異星人の侵略次元生物に対処できるようにする
If it's cancer, let it fight the cancer
ガンならガンと闘わせろ
But don't kill your own cells
ただし自分の細胞を殺さないでください
then become a big
それから大きくなる
an important area
重要な領域
Then I will briefly introduce
それでは簡単にご紹介します
immune system
免疫系
all immune cells
すべての免疫細胞
it has an immune
それは免疫を持っています
Blast cells that we call bone marrow
骨髄と呼ばれる芽球細胞
hematopoietic stem cells
造血幹細胞
Called Hematopoietis stem cells
造血幹細胞と呼ばれる
In adults these hematopoietic stem cells
成人ではこれらの造血幹細胞が
is the marrow in our bones
私たちの骨の髄です
Look at the red bone marrow
赤い骨髄を見てください
That hematopoietic stem cell
その造血幹細胞
It will be divided into two categories
2つのカテゴリーに分かれます
Myeloid Globlasts
骨髄球芽細胞
or lymphoblast
またはリンパ芽球
bone marrow blast
骨髄芽球
responsible for making our blood cells
私たちの血球を作る責任があります
erythrocyte
紅血球
it has a lot of phagocytes
食細胞がたくさんある
We are called white blood cells
私たちは白血球と呼ばれています
so you see white blood cells
それで白血球が見えます
Another large group we call lymphoblasts
私たちがリンパ芽球と呼ぶもう一つの大きなグループ
These lymphoblasts are responsible for making T lymphocytes
これらのリンパ芽球は T リンパ球の生成を担当します
And B lymphocytes
そしてBリンパ球
Everyone has heard of antibodies
誰もが抗体について聞いたことがあるでしょう
Antibodies are mainly after activation of B lymphocytes
抗体は主にBリンパ球の活性化後に生成されます。
These proteins that are produced and secreted into the blood
生成され血液中に分泌されるこれらのタンパク質
Can recognize external whys
外部の理由を認識できる
entire immune system
免疫システム全体
The most important category is probably this
最も重要なカテゴリはおそらくこれです
that you want to phagocyte
貪食したいということ
Phagocyte encounters bacteria within the first instant
食細胞は最初の瞬間に細菌に遭遇します
devour it
それをむさぼり食う
We use the following reality to explain
以下の現実を使って説明します
Write a few slides for everyone to see
全員が見られるようにスライドをいくつか書きます
This is seen with an electron microscope
電子顕微鏡で見るとこんな感じ
This is a white blood cell
これは白血球です
erythrocyte
紅血球
Red blood cells are much more numerous than white blood cells
赤血球は白血球よりはるかに数が多い
So let's look at red first
それでは、最初に赤を見てみましょう
It is difficult for you to distinguish the electronic behavior of white blood cells
白血球の電子的挙動を区別するのは困難です
Which are phagocytes
食細胞とは何ですか
Which ones are mention cells? They look similar
どのセルが言及されていますか? 見た目は似ています
But if you do some special dyeing
でも特殊な染色をすると
Like the hematology department, he can go to draw blood after it comes out
血液内科のように、血液が出た後に採血に行くことができます。
He can do some special dyes and you'll see this form
彼は特別な染色を行うことができ、この形が表示されます。
Let's say these are red blood cells
これが赤血球だとしましょう
Those are the white blood cells.
それが白血球です。
You see, the white blood cells look different, but here they look the same
ほら、白血球は違って見えますが、ここでは同じように見えます
It doesn't look the same on this side, it's just a four-neutral
こちら側は同じようには見えません、ただの4ニュートラルです
leukocyte
白血球
This is a mononuclear ball
これは単核球です
Then this should be a four-acid white blood cell
そうすると、これは四酸白血球になるはずです
If you get leukemia
白血病になったら
you'll find that certain types of this
これの特定のタイプがあることがわかります
A large increase in the number of white blood cells
白血球数の大幅な増加
Next, I will introduce to you
次にご紹介させていただくのは
I clearly want to know how to deal with foreigners for a living
外国人とどう接して生きていけばいいのか知りたい
Everyone, look at this secret
みなさん、この秘密を見てください
These tubular systems
これらの管状システム
These are called lymphatic vessels
これらはリンパ管と呼ばれます
And what about these little black balls?
では、この小さな黒いボールはどうでしょうか？
want lymph nodes
リンパ節が欲しい
After the blood cells are made from that bone marrow
その骨髄から血球が作られた後
climbed into the blood vessel
血管に入り込んだ
Then search for blood vessels all over the body
次に、体中の血管を調べます。
with lymphatic circulation
リンパ循環とともに
first person to find it
最初に見つけた人
if found
見つかったら
It sends out the function of going straight to destroy the invading creatures
侵入生物を排除する機能を発信する
can't find it
見つからない
it has a certain lifespan
一定の寿命がある
it will die
それは死ぬだろう
after death
死後
Our modeling mother cells continue to make these white blood cells
私たちのモデリング母細胞はこれらの白血球を作り続けます
So let's maintain a certain balance
だから一定のバランスを保ちましょう
if cancer
がんの場合
Chemo here has serious side effects
ここでの化学療法には深刻な副作用がある
That is, it will cause the white blood cells to drop
つまり白血球が減少してしまうのです
Of course this becomes very susceptible to nosocomial infections
当然、院内感染を起こしやすくなります。
In fact, because chemotherapy drugs will kill our hematopoietic mother cells
実際、化学療法薬は造血母細胞を殺すため、
After killing, its ability to produce white blood cells declines
殺した後は白血球を生成する能力が低下する
will become less
少なくなるでしょう
So these phagocytes in our body
つまり、私たちの体内のこれらの食細胞は、
It will be the first time of course there are aliens as creatures once invaded
かつて侵略された生物としてエイリアンが存在するのはもちろん初めてとなる
It will be the first time these alien creatures
このような外来生物が登場するのは初めてだ
swallow
飲み込む
So everyone phagocytes
だからみんな貪食するんだよ
I'll show you this video later
このビデオは後で紹介します
After swallowing, of course, many bacteria are controlled in this way
もちろん飲み込んだ後も、このようにして多くの細菌が抑制されます
But some are more pathogenic
しかし、より病原性のあるものもあります
it is not afraid of phagocytes
食細胞を恐れない
Like the phagocytic cells I mentioned, it has another characteristic
先ほどの貪食細胞と同様に、もう一つの特徴があります。
it will after phagocytosis bacteria
それは細菌の貪食後に起こります
it transforms into what are called antigen presenting cells
いわゆる抗原提示細胞に変化します。
It will carry this germ, the devoured germ
それはこの細菌を運ぶでしょう、食べられた細菌
Enter the 08 system
08システムを入力してください
Go to Section 08
セクション08に進む
In Section 08, it will encounter the T cell just mentioned
セクション08では、先ほどのT細胞と遭遇します。
Then this antigen presenting cell is exposed to activate 08 cell in section 08
次に、この抗原提示細胞はセクション 08 で 08 細胞を活性化するために露出されます。
triggers a germ-specific immune response
細菌特異的な免疫反応を引き起こす
Then what about these 08 cells
では、この08細胞はどうなるのでしょうか？
Through blood circulation and 08 circulation
血液循環と08循環を通じて
find invading bacteria
侵入した細菌を見つける
destroy it
それを破壊する
This is how all our immune systems work
これが私たちのすべての免疫システムの仕組みです
Then I will show you the video now
それでは、今からビデオをお見せします
this is a phagocyte
これは食細胞です
an electron to kill bacteria
細菌を殺すための電子
a microscope film
顕微鏡のビデオ
wait a minute
等一下等一下
Here spread a neutrophil is
ここに広がる好中球は
red blood cells in the middle
真ん中の赤血球
Because some people may not understand English well
英語がよくわからない人もいるかもしれないので
i was explaining
私は説明していました
This is a four middle white blood cell
これは真ん中の 4 つの白血球です
it's just bacteria
それはただの細菌です
it's just red blood cells
それはただの赤血球です
Staphylococcus aureus
黄色ブドウ球菌
start chasing this
これを追いかけ始める
Chemicals in the middle of bacteria four
細菌 4 の真ん中にある化学物質
attract it to chase
追いかけるように引き寄せる
So the Uighurs it produces are called phagocytes
したがって、それが生み出すウイグル人は貪食細胞と呼ばれます
So it's called a phagocyte
だから食細胞って言うんだよ
right
右
oh no
なんてこった
this it has some that
これにはそれがいくつかあります
that
それか
Adjustment
調整
so you see it says
こう書いてあるのがわかりますか
if you use those
それらを使用する場合
To see our body's detailed multi-dimensional organisms
私たちの体の詳細な多次元有機体を見るため
Once the software is hacked
ソフトウェアがハッキングされると
Phagocytes will immediately
食細胞はすぐに
become a cell
細胞になる
so it is
それはそうです
After hacking software
ソフトウェアをハッキングした後
Phagocytes immediately go after it
食細胞はすぐにそれを追いかけます
that swallows it up
それはそれを飲み込む
After talking about devouring
むさぼり食う話をした後
it will go to section 08 first
最初にセクション08に進みます
present antigen to cells
抗原を細胞に提示する
so this is the first step
これが最初のステップです
Phagocytosis
食作用
ok then let's
わかりました、それではしましょう
look at
見る
next
次
Subtitler Zither Harp
字幕製作人Zither Harp
Well, here, this one looks like bacteria, over there hairs, bacteria are completely different from our human cells
ほら、これはバクテリアのように見えます、あそこの髪の毛、バクテリアは私たちの人間の細胞とはまったく異なります
So for the immune system, this job is very easy, it is very easy, it is easy to distinguish which are bacteria and which are cells of our limbs
つまり、免疫システムにとって、この仕事は非常に簡単で、どれが細菌でどれが四肢の細胞であるかを区別するのは簡単です。
It does not attack its own cells, it attacks bacteria, and bacteria have some special structures, which we call pathogen-associated molecular structures
それ自体の細胞を攻撃するのではなく、細菌を攻撃します。細菌は、病原体関連分子構造と呼ばれるいくつかの特別な構造を持っています。
Those who speak English don’t need to read it, because the fraiserin means to become hairy
フライセリンは毛むくじゃらになるという意味なので、英語ができる人は読む必要はありません。
Then there are some components called lipopolisaccharide, cell B, bacterial cell B, human cells do not have cell B
それから、リポ多糖、細胞B、細菌細胞Bと呼ばれるいくつかの成分がありますが、人間の細胞には細胞Bはありません
So of course there is no lps, but the plate below is its receptor, the receptor that recognizes these molecular structures
もちろん lps はありませんが、下のプレートはその受容体、つまりこれらの分子構造を認識する受容体です。
Some of these receptors recognize different molecular structures
これらの受容体の一部は異なる分子構造を認識します
So this is the principle why our phagocytic cells can find bacteria and viruses to swallow them
これが、私たちの食細胞が細菌やウイルスを見つけて飲み込むことができる原理です
Phagocytosis when bacteria just don't see V. aureus being phagocytized by our secondary neutrophils
二次好中球による黄色ブドウ球菌の貪食を細菌が認識できない場合の貪食作用
One thing happens after devouring
むさぼり食った後に起こることは一つ
Just looking for our artist, is it a big principle or how bacteria phagocytosis
私たちのアーティストを探しています。それは大きな原理ですか、それとも細菌の貪食の仕組みですか
It will have a different molecular structure on the bacteria due to phagocytosis
貪食作用により細菌上では異なる分子構造を持ちます。
In addition to devouring it, it actually activates it
それを貪り食うだけでなく、実際にそれを活性化します
it gets fierce
激しくなる
It's pretty empty after phagocytizing bacteria
バクテリアを貪食した後はかなり空っぽになります
an activated phagocyte
活性化された食細胞
Activated phagocytes have
活性化された食細胞は、
Ability to present antigens to T cells
T細胞に抗原を提示する能力
If you are just one of these
あなたがこれらのうちの 1 人に過ぎない場合
original antigenicity
本来の抗原性
It presents to T cells that function is actually poor
実際に機能が低下していることをT細胞に示します
What about activated antigen-presenting cells?
活性化された抗原提示細胞はどうでしょうか?
It can present antigens, which are derived from bacteria
細菌に由来する抗原を提示することができます
right if it's kennzer
ケンツァーならそうだね
tumor antigen
腫瘍抗原
But, it also needs to represent co-stimulatory molecules
ただし、共刺激分子を表す必要もあります
It has to represent cell technology
細胞技術を表すものでなければなりません
This is only activated
これは有効化するだけです
Phagocytes, which look fierce, have this ability
凶暴そうに見える食細胞にはこの能力がある
Then
それから
Next this activated phagocyte
次にこの活性化された食細胞
I just talked about antigens, it shows antigens, a little bit of red
先ほど抗原について話しました。抗原が示されています。少し赤くなっています。
co-stimulatory molecular cell technology
共刺激分子細胞技術
act together on a single T cell
T細胞に対して一緒に作用する
When T cells activate
T細胞が活性化すると
Split
分裂
differentiation
分化
he lived a long time
彼は長生きした
What about T cells like this?
このようなT細胞はどうでしょうか？
He was also a very kind T cell
彼はとても優しいT細胞でもありました
After being educated by antigen presenting cells
抗原提示細胞による教育後
He'll also turn into an empty T-cell
彼も空のT細胞になるだろう
and he will split
そして彼は別れるだろう
He has an immunity, that system has a characteristic
彼には免疫がある、そのシステムには特徴がある
that is, T cells
つまりT細胞です
A certain type of T cell, such as the T cell activated by this bacterium
特定の種類の T 細胞（この細菌によって活性化される T 細胞など）
He can only recognize this bacterium
彼はこの細菌しか認識できない
He doesn't care about other enemies
彼は他の敵のことなど気にしていない
For example, if I'm working on the hepatitis B virus
たとえば、B型肝炎ウイルスの研究をしているとします。
What if antigenic phagocytes present this hepatitis B virus
抗原性食細胞がこの B 型肝炎ウイルスを提示したらどうなるでしょうか
antigen to this T cell
このT細胞に対する抗原
The trained T cells only recognize liver B
訓練された T 細胞は肝臓 B のみを認識します
He doesn't care about other enemies
彼は他の敵のことなど気にしていない
This is what vaccines do
ワクチンってこういうことするんだな
After we have a certain vaccine
特定のワクチンができた後
these immune responses
これらの免疫反応
Only recognize this vaccine
このワクチンのみを認識します
other viruses
他のウイルス
sorry he doesn't care
ごめんなさい、彼は気にしません
So we have to find the right antigen
したがって、適切な抗原を見つける必要があります
to elicit a response to this antigen
この抗原に対する反応を引き出すために
T cell response
T細胞反応
That
それか
microorganism
微生物
You can easily know what his antigen is
彼の抗原が何であるかを簡単に知ることができます
But cancer is hard for you to know
しかし、がんはあなたにはわかりにくいものです
cancer cells
cancer i細胞
It's actually a change in your own cells
それは実際にはあなた自身の細胞の変化です
It's actually very, very similar to your own cells
実はそれはあなた自身の細胞と非常によく似ています
I just talked about the immune system
免疫システムについてお話しました
actually training
実際にトレーニングする
exist
存在
in the process of growing
成長の過程で
it will have received an education
それは教育を受けているだろう
We call it negative selection
私たちはそれをネガティブセレクションと呼んでいます
in immune cells
免疫細胞の中で
Trained in T cells
T細胞で訓練された
It does not recognize antigens on its own cells
自身の細胞上の抗原を認識しません
avoid autoimmune disease
自己免疫疾患を避ける
But because the i cells are different from your own cells
でもi細胞は自分の細胞とは違うから
almost the same
ほぼ同じ
So the immune system basically doesn't recognize him
つまり免疫系は基本的に彼を認識しない
or don't want to know him
あるいは彼のことを知りたくない
In this situation
この状況では
Is there a way to train the immune system
免疫システムを鍛える方法はありますか
separate
別
because of i-cell disease
i細胞病のせいで
Now scientific research is more and more clear
現在、科学的研究はますます明らかになってきています
found that although it looks a lot alike
見た目はよく似ているにもかかわらず、
but not exactly the same
しかし全く同じではありません
Because if it's exactly the same it won't become a cancer cell
全く同じならガン細胞にならないから
So we find some differences
したがって、いくつかの違いが見つかります
train your immune system
免疫システムを訓練する
to identify these differences
これらの違いを特定するには
if it really works
本当に効果があるなら
It can specifically attack cancer cells
がん細胞を特異的に攻撃することができる
Achieve the effect of healing Kensel
ケンゼルを治癒する効果を得る
So there is actually a concept here
実はここにコンセプトがあります
The immune system is inactive under normal conditions
免疫システムは通常の状態では不活性です
It only activates when it touches an enemy
敵に触れた時のみ発動する
when the enemy is eliminated
敵が排除されたとき
It means that those activated cells will die in large numbers
活性化された細胞が大量に死滅することを意味します
So this is what was just said
それで、これが今言われたことです
These T cells have several properties
これらの T 細胞にはいくつかの特性があります
the first one it will split a lot
最初のものは大きく分割されます
When you encounter, say, the hepatitis B virus
たとえばB型肝炎ウイルスに遭遇したとき
To deal with liver B, the T cells will divide in large numbers
肝臓Bに対処するために、T細胞が大量に分裂します
This number becomes many
この数は多くなります
You can effectively control invasive sanitary species
衛生種の侵入を効果的に制御できます
The second is medical expertise
2つ目は医療の専門知識です
activated T cells
活性化されたT細胞
I only know this one virus that invaded
侵入したウイルスはこの 1 つだけです
it doesn't care
気にしない
So sometimes we have to get a lot of vaccines
そのため、時には大量のワクチンを接種しなければならないこともあります
play a dozen
1ダースプレイする
train different T cells
さまざまな T 細胞を訓練する
different G8,G9 cells
異なる G8、G9 細胞
against different bacteria
さまざまな細菌に対して
and memory
そして記憶
after a vaccination
ワクチン接種後
some are lifetime
生涯にわたるものもある
Because T cells are constantly replicating molecules by themselves
T細胞は常に自ら分子を複製しているため
knitting
編み物
So when we meet again next time
ということで、次回またお会いした時は
It can be trained very quickly
とても早くトレーニングできる
So it has these basic properties
したがって、これらの基本的な特性を備えています
Expertise and memory
専門知識と記憶力
this is very good
これはすごくいい
because our cancer cells
なぜなら私たちのがん細胞は
We want to train T cells
T細胞を鍛えたい
only medical
医療のみ
it only targets cancer cells
がん細胞だけをターゲットにする
not to deal with our normal cells
私たちの正常な細胞を扱わないこと
memory is also very good
記憶力もとても良いです
your metastatic cancer cells
あなたの転移性がん細胞
not yet killed
まだ殺されていない
But we have T cells if they are still there
しかし、T細胞がまだ存在するなら、私たちにもT細胞は存在します。
It can help you train again in the long run
長期的には再びトレーニングするのに役立ちます
Then you don't care where the diversion is to hide
そうすれば、気晴らしがどこに隠れているかは気にしません
Your T-C bag can track it
T-Cバッグは追跡できます
Then achieve the effect of long-term control
長期的な制御効果を実現します
like just saw that mouse
あのネズミを見ているような気分だ
It actually has cancer cells
実はガン細胞がいる
But because it has a sound immune system, it is not afraid
でも免疫力がしっかりしているから怖くない
It can still maintain a roughly healthy state of life
ほぼ健康的な生活状態を維持できる
Then let me show you
それではお見せしましょう
It's the trained T-C bag, it's useless to stay in Section 08
鍛えられたT-Cバッグだ、セクション08に居ても無駄だ
Because its enemy is not in the 08 section
敵はセクション08にいないから
It goes to find its invading vitamins, which are bacteria.
侵入してきたビタミンであるバクテリアを探しに行きます。
If it's a cancer cell, it finds the metastatic cancer cells
がん細胞であれば、転移性がん細胞を見つけます。
It can't just stay in section 08
セクション08だけに留まるわけにはいかない
Then there are some complicated principles
それから、いくつかの複雑な原則があります
then i will describe a little bit
それから少し説明します
watch a video later
後でビデオを見る
That's a viral infection
それはウイルス感染症です
1 The phagocytic cell will of course swallow it
1 食細胞は当然それを飲み込みます
After swallowing it, it will also be at the site of the infection
飲み込んだ後は感染部位にもなります
inflammatory reaction
炎症反応
Inflammatory reaction?
炎症反応？
At this time, there will actually be some
このとき、実際にはいくつかのことがあります。
compartmentalizing hormone and adsorbin
ホルモンと吸着剤を区画する
present at the site of infection
感染部位に存在する
capillaries
微血管
above blood vessels
血管の上
these in the blood
血の中のこれら
White blood cells when it goes in
白血球が通過するとき
It interacts with these adsorbed proteins
これらの吸着タンパク質と相互作用します
Then the white blood cells
すると白血球が
Can
できる
won't leave so quickly
そんなに早く離れないだろう
It rolls over the infection site
感染部位を転がる
out of shape
形が崩れて
divert transfer into our organization
私たちの組織への転送を転送する
compartmentalization
区画化
find inflamed tissue
炎症を起こした組織を見つける
The inflamed tissue is actually the site of the infection.
炎症を起こした組織は実際には感染部位です。
Then by looping like this
次に、このようにループすることで
can be expelled from the blood vessel
血管から来る可能性があります
leave blood vessel
血管を残す
Find where the enemy is attacking
敵が攻撃している場所を見つける
If it's cancer, find the cancer cells
がんならがん細胞を見つけよう
If it is a bacterial infection, find the site of the bacterial infection
細菌感染の場合は、細菌感染部位を特定します。
to destroy it
それを破壊する
OK, let's see what happens next.
さて、次に何が起こるか見てみましょう。
then you cut the video
それからビデオをカットします
Lukasite is white
ルカサイトは白です
Usually it's inside a blood vessel
通常は血管内にあります
It's the inflamed area
炎症を起こしている部分です
Bacterial infection releases cytokines
細菌感染によりサイトカインが放出される
blood vessels at the site of infection
感染部位の血管
Expressed Adsorbin
発現されたアドソルビン
to break
壊す
Appraisal component
鑑合成分
Identify the parts of the ingredients
原材料の部位を特定する
make them close
彼らを近づける
sugars on white blood cells
白血球上の糖
combine
結合
They start rolling in the veins
彼らは静脈内を転がり始める
sugars on white blood cells
白血球上の糖
or by cell
または携帯電話で
really insist
本当に主張します
Enter
入力
then the inflamed area
次に炎症を起こしている部分
Parts that have not been identified
特定されていない部品
Then find the inflamed site, which is the site of bacterial infection, and eliminate it
次に、細菌感染部位である炎症部位を見つけて除去します。
it's a live animation
それはライブアニメーションです
Here everyone see, this is an artery
ここ、皆さん見てください、これは動脈です
This is the front
こちらが正面です
This direction is the direction of blood flow
この方向が血流の方向です
Probably the flow speed is very fast, but in fact there are many, many blood cells
おそらく流速は非常に速いと思われますが、実際には血球が非常に多く存在します。
Then some white blood cells are absorbed here
その後、白血球の一部がここで吸収されます
some of them have entered the organization
彼らの何人かは組織に入った
You see, all these blood cells are absorbed in the veins
ご存知のとおり、これらの血球はすべて静脈に吸収されます
The arterial bleeds, blood cells cannot absorb
動脈が出血すると血球が吸収できなくなります
thanks then , some are crawling
ありがとう、それでは、いくつかは這っています
some have gone in
何人かは入ってきました
then if you
もしあなたが
This, this has entered the organization
これ、これが組織に入りました
This has entered your organization
これがあなたの組織に入りました
out of blood vessels into tissue
血管から組織へ
It is for you to see the cells inside the blood vessel
血管の中の細胞を見るためのものです
clamp the blood vessels
血管をクランプする
So you see, so many cells can't flow now
わかりますか、非常に多くの細胞が今は流れることができません
So you can see, very, very cells inside that blood vessel
つまり、血管内の非常に非常に多くの細胞が見えるのです
then turn it on
それからそれをオンにします
blood starts flowing again
血液が再び流れ始める
As soon as you let it go, it starts flowing again
手を放すとまた流れ始める
So our blood vessels are full of these blood vessels
つまり、私たちの血管はこれらの血管で満たされています
So, the T cells after education
つまり、教育後の T 細胞は
Involved in blood vessels
血管に関与している
Then, through the effect just mentioned called adsorption
次に、今述べた吸着と呼ばれる効果により、
find the enemy it wants to attack
攻撃したい敵を見つける
then go in and destroy it
それから入って破壊してください
ok , let ' s see next
さて、次を見ましょう
Lukasites are white blood cells
ルカサイトは白血球です
ok then next
はい、それでは次へ
Actually I don't know
実際のところは分かりません
But it doesn’t seem to be because oil should be fat, it’s in the blood, I think
でも、それは油が脂肪であるはずがあるからではないようです、それは血液中にあると思います
When it is very oily, there will be a lot of that and that lipid in it
油分が多いと、あれやこれやの脂質が多く含まれます。
Will this ingredient be in it?
この成分は入っているのでしょうか？
It causes the blood cells not to absorb and don’t imagine that the principle of water pipes is not the same
血球が吸収されなくなりますが、水道管の原理が同じではないことを想像しないでください。
But will it be true? In fact, when we do science, there is evidence to speak for itself. So
しかし、それは本当でしょうか? 実際、科学を行うと、それ自体を物語る証拠が得られます。
don't know
わかりません
but
しかし
It must be bad for your health
きっと健康に悪いはずです
especially for that new blood vessel
特に新しい血管に対しては
sure it must be bad
確かにダメなはずだ
then next is
じゃあ次は
Didn't he just go in
彼はただ入ってきたんじゃないの？
Is the inflamed area right?
炎症箇所は大丈夫ですか？
So if you find that infected cell, how does he kill him?
それでは、感染した細胞を見つけたら、どうやって殺すのでしょうか?
show him next
次に彼に見せてください
current
現在
this this video this is a
このビデオはこれです
electron microscope photo
電子顕微鏡写真
A is the target cell is the Target Cell
A はターゲット セルです。 はターゲット セルです。
So this could be a virus-infected cell
つまり、これはウイルスに感染した細胞である可能性があります
or cancer cells
または癌細胞
Then this CTL
次に、このCTL
These are called killer T cells
これらはキラーT細胞と呼ばれます
Here I am called T cell, this is it
ここで私はT細胞と呼ばれています、これがそれです
Then it recognizes the antigen by this
するとこれで抗原を認識します
followed by T cell binding
続いてT細胞結合
Atrophy of target cells after binding
結合後の標的細胞の萎縮
Within minutes the target cells begin to shrink
数分以内に標的細胞が縮小し始める
Because after it combines it will dissolve some mold
結合した後、一部のカビを溶かしてしまうため
combined it creates a channel
組み合わせてチャネルを作成します
Let this killer, some lytic mold in this T cell
このキラー、溶解性カビをこの T 細胞に入れましょう
Injected through this channel
このチャネルを通じて注入される
This target cell to attack
この攻撃対象の細胞
Then the dissolving mold will work after it goes in.
そして、溶けたカビは入った後に役割を果たします。
Let the target cell start shrinking in a few minutes
数分以内にターゲットセルが縮小し始めるようにします
Then its cell membrane will form some protruding small bubbles
その後、その細胞膜はいくつかの突き出た小さな泡を形成します
Then the last cell dies
そして最後の細胞が死ぬ
die
死亡
After that, everyone, everyone, look at the holes one by one.
その後、皆さん、穴を一つずつ見てください。
this is in
これは入っています
Add ginger cells to break through
ショウガの細胞を加えて突破する
what is this cell
この細胞は何ですか
this is the whole process
これがプロセス全体です
I'll come then
じゃあ行きます
control the time
時間をコントロールする
We haven't even talked about the protagonist Ai Zheng yet.
主人公のアイ・ジェンについてはまだ話していません。
Don't let him talk for so long
彼にそんなに長く話させないでください
Let everyone see it directly
みんなに直接見てもらいましょう
good
良い
This is a white blood cell
これは白血球です
This is a T cell
これはT細胞です
This is the target cell, the antigen on it
これが標的細胞、その上の抗原です
then after combining it with
それを組み合わせた後
will dissolve some concentrated mold
濃縮されたカビの一部を溶解します
inject into
に注入する
target cell
標的細胞
that makes the target cell die
それは標的細胞を死滅させる
we'll see next
次に見てみましょう
there should be one
あるべきです
This is a virus-infected cell
これはウイルスに感染した細胞です
before he was killed
彼が殺される前に
He keeps releasing these viruses
彼はこれらのウイルスを放出し続けます
He will kill himself and the virus will come out
彼は自殺するだろう、そうすればウイルスが出てくるだろう
We kill after TGPOL passes
TGPOLが通過したら殺す
Of course he won't know about the virus after killing it
もちろんウイルスを殺した後はウイルスのことを知らないだろう
So this is a principle of controlling viral infection
これがウイルス感染を制御する原則です
He has electron microscope pictures next
彼は次に電子顕微鏡写真を持っています
This is one of his Target Sales
これは彼の目標売上の 1 つです
This is white shoes
これは白い靴です
after combining
組み合わせた後
He now has a channel called Bridge
彼は現在、Bridge というチャンネルを持っています
dissolve some mold
カビを溶かす
everyone see
誰もが見る
inject it
それを注入する
After injection, it causes the shrinkage of the target cells
注射後、標的細胞が収縮します。
the cell membrane
細胞膜
transmission
伝染 ; 感染
look at it
それを見てください
in transmission
送信中
In the end, the cell is too big to die.
最終的に、細胞は死ぬには大きすぎます。
produce some small bubbles, then decompose
小さな泡が発生し、その後分解します
This T cell, it can find its next enemy
この T 細胞は次の敵を見つけることができます
If this is an I cell, that's hopefully going to happen
これが I 細胞なら、うまくいけばそうなるだろう
And it's I cells, wherever they hide, T cells have the ability to find them
それは I 細胞です、どこに隠れていても、T 細胞はそれを見つける能力を持っています
Next, what is immunotherapy?
次に免疫療法とは何でしょうか？
The first one is really using your own body
1つ目は実際に自分の体を使うことです
In fact, it should be that you use your own body's immune system
実際には、自分自身の体の免疫システムを利用する必要があります。
to cure disease
病気を治すために
immunotherapy
免疫療法
Here are some examples
ここではいくつかの例を示します
or immune watermelon, or immune-related proteins
または免疫スイカ、または免疫関連タンパク質
To treat a disease, it's called immunotherapy
病気を治療することを免疫療法といいます
There are two categories, active immunotherapy and passive immunotherapy
能動免疫療法と受動免疫療法の 2 つのカテゴリーがあります
Active is immunotherapy, that is, using some drugs or vaccines
アクティブとは免疫療法、つまりいくつかの薬やワクチンを使用することです。
Activate the patient's own immune miniature
患者自身の免疫ミニチュアを活性化する
That is to say, this immune miniature is actually not stimulated, but stimulated.
つまり、この免疫ミニチュアは実際には刺激されているのではなく、刺激されているのです。
For example, the vaccine itself does not have the ability to resist bacteria
たとえば、ワクチン自体には細菌に対する抵抗力はありません。
It triggers the immune system of the immunized person, and it produces a protective effect
免疫を受けた人の免疫システムを活性化し、防御効果を生み出します。
So the real active people are produced by the vaccine
つまり、本当の活動的な人々はワクチンによって生み出されるのです
So this is what we call active immunization, for example, you are injected with type B liver cancer vaccine
これが能動免疫と呼ばれるもので、たとえば B 型肝がんワクチンを注射されます。
Afterwards, the injected baby will produce specialized comprehensive antibodies
その後、注射された赤ちゃんは特殊な包括的な抗体を生成します
Then it is no longer afraid of hepatitis B virus infection
そうすればB型肝炎ウイルス感染も怖くなくなります
So this antibody is produced by the baby, not injected by us
つまり、この抗体は赤ちゃんによって産生されるものであり、私たちが注射したものではありません
So this is what we call active immunotherapy
これが能動免疫療法と呼ばれるものです
Then there are some critical situations
その後、いくつかの危機的な状況が発生します
Because it takes a while for a vaccine to develop
ワクチンの開発には時間がかかるため、
Then when you are infected by a virus
それでウイルスに感染したら
it can't wait that long
そんなに長く待つことはできません
it just keeps replicating
それは複製を続けるだけです
Waiting until your grass is not easy to produce is already bad
草が生えにくくなるまで待っているのはすでに悪いことです
So when you say you accidentally get rubbed on your body
だから、うっかり体をこすってしまったというときは
And know that this is like the love stagnation virus
そしてこれは愛の停滞ウイルスのようなものだと知ってください
There is this heteromorphic hepatic heart virus
この異型肝心ウイルスというのがあります
Then you can no longer use vaccines at this time
そうなると現時点ではワクチンは使用できなくなります
Because it's too late
もう手遅れだから
At this time, a large amount of antibodies are injected into the
このとき、体内に大量の抗体が注入されます。
So this antibody is produced by our event
つまり、この抗体は私たちのイベントによって生成されたものです
then type in
次に入力します
So is tetanus
破傷風もそうだよ
you got rubbed by that rusty nail
あなたはその錆びた釘で擦られました
Hurry up and call
急いで電話してください
That tetanus is vaccinated
破傷風の予防接種を受けていること
but some are poisonous
しかし中には有毒なものもあります
Snake venom is directly injected with snake venom serum
ヘビ毒血清をヘビ毒に直接注入
Synthesize the bacteria or virus
細菌やウイルスを合成する
or these toxins they produce
またはそれらが生成する毒素
This is called passive immunity
これを受動免疫といいます
are now used as cancer immunizers
現在はがんの免疫剤として使用されています
The next example in this period will come to an end.
次の例は終わります
our body's immune system
私たちの体の免疫システム
The immune person that everyone does not know in the body
体の中の誰もが知らない免疫力のある人
It turned out to be so effective
とても効果があることが分かりました
But his example might scare me
でも彼の例は私を怖がらせるかもしれない
in roman times
ローマ時代に
The average human life span is only in their 20s
人間の平均寿命はわずか20代
His so-called life is
彼のいわゆる人生とは、
as long as you are born
あなたが生まれている限り
with death
死とともに
The death of the little baby is also counted
小さな赤ちゃんの死もカウントされる
because at that time
なぜならその時は
think about it
考えてみてください
that's us now
それが今の私たちです
Born in Taiwan
台湾生まれ
You get a dozen different vaccines
十数種類のワクチンを接種できる
why? because
なぜ?なぜなら
Babies are very susceptible to infection
赤ちゃんは感染症に非常に弱い
He may have received his mother in the first half of the year
他一開始前半年可能受母
mother protection
母親の保護
if breastfeeding
授乳中の場合
but after that
しかしその後
He needs to immunize himself
彼は自分で予防接種を受ける必要がある
to protect himself
自分自身を守るために
But for a while, it's actually quite dangerous
しかし、しばらくの間、それは実際には非常に危険です
So need to be vaccinated
だからワクチン接種が必要だ
to accelerate the effect of this protection
この保護の効果を加速するために
Even in medieval England in the 1500s
1500年代の中世イギリスでも
Its overall average condition is still around 30 years
全体的な平均状態はまだ30年ほどです。
it's been a long time now
もう長い時間が経ちました
Now both Japan and Taiwan are 80 years old
日本も台湾も建国80周年を迎えました
But some countries are still at 50
しかし、一部の国はまだ50歳です
In fact, this is a very important human invention
実際、これは非常に重要な人類の発明です
is the vaccine
ワクチンです
I just said that vaccines are actually active immunity.
先ほど、ワクチンは実際には能動免疫であると言いました。
You see how well this vaccine protects us
このワクチンが私たちをいかによく守っているかがわかります
These are what you see in Taiwan
台湾ではこんな光景が見られます
Almost the world's little despicable
ほぼ世界で最も卑劣な
vaccines to be given
投与されるワクチン
For example, like the small ringgit vaccine
たとえば、少額リンギットのワクチンのように
Over 21,000 cases in 1952
1952年には21,000件以上の症例
now zero
今はゼロ
You see everything else is like this
他はすべてこんな感じです
so in the 1950s
それで1950年代に
If you look at the top ten causes of death
死因トップ10を見てみると
definitely more like
間違いなくもっと好きです
completely different now
現在完全不一樣
Many of these infectious diseases should be
これらの感染症の多くは、
So the shape of human disease is changing
人間の病気の形が変わりつつある
the vaccine was invented
ワクチンが発明された
So our lifespan is extended
それで私たちの寿命は延びる
After the extension, we will face another form of disease
延長後は別の病気に直面することになる
cancer
癌
So now cancer is our worst enemy
つまり今、ガンは私たちの最大の敵なのです
But come to think of it, vaccines
でも、考えてみれば、ワクチンって
Help us deal with the top killers of our past
過去のトップ殺人者たちに対処するのに協力してください
Is there any way to use the same method now
同じ方法を現在使用する方法はありますか
to activate the immune system
免疫システムを活性化するために
Then it's not about dealing with alien dimensional creatures at this time.
そうすると、現時点では異次元の生物を扱う話ではありません。
It's to deal with the cancer cells after the transformation of your body's cells
体の細胞が変化した後のがん細胞に対処するためです
Is there a way for the immune system to achieve this character?
免疫システムがこの性質を達成する方法はあるのでしょうか?
So we're going to introduce you to
それでは紹介していきます
Then the system he uses is just introduced to you
それでは、彼が使用しているシステムを紹介します。
What are these killers?
これらの殺人者は何ですか？
Phagocytes or T cells
食細胞またはT細胞
still these things
まだこれらのこと
good
良い
Here are the top 10 causes of death
死因トップ10はこちら
Cancer is now number one
がんが今ナンバーワン
Probably close to 30%
おそらく30％近く
But it wasn't like that in the 1950s
しかし、1950年代にはそうではありませんでした
That's because a lot of the big part is the vaccine development wages
それは、重要な部分の多くはワクチン開発の賃金だからです
Next comes cancer cells, cancer
次はがん細胞、がんです
Cancer doesn't just pop up out of thin air.
がんは何もないところから突然発生するわけではありません。
In fact, it is also a process, because many of you should know
実際、それはプロセスでもあります。なぜなら、多くの人が知っているはずです。
everyone has culture theory
誰もが文化を持っているという理論
try to survive in the earth environment
地球環境の中で生き延びようとする
Organisms best suited to this environment can survive
この環境に最も適した生物は生き残ることができます
When the environment changes you need to have some mutation
環境が変わると突然変異が必要になる
Some genetic variation is required
ある程度の遺伝的変異が必要
This mutation makes you more suitable for this environment
この突然変異により、あなたはこの環境により適したものになります
In this group, probably most of the members of the group died
このグループでは、おそらくグループのメンバーのほとんどが死亡しました
These organisms can stay because they are suitable for this environment
これらの生物はこの環境に適しているから生き残ることができる
This is called things, those who live in peace, those who live in the world
これを物と言う、空を静める者、世界に生きる者が生きる
Cancer cells are actually produced in this way
がん細胞は実際にこのようにして作られます
This edited theory of what we call cancer
私たちが癌と呼ぶものについてのこの編集された理論
I will use this very complicated picture to introduce it to him.
この非常に複雑な写真を使って彼に紹介します。
The gray cells are some normal cells
灰色の細胞は正常な細胞です
when it's stimulated by a number of different carcinogens
さまざまな発がん物質によって刺激された場合
Of course it will transform, and some will turn into cancer cells
もちろん変形しますし、一部はガン細胞になります
So I just said that many people may have cancer cells physiologically
つまり、多くの人が生理学的に癌細胞を持っている可能性があると言いました。
But in the early days, during the elimination period
しかし初期の頃、排除期間中に
We have a very good and sound Burmese system here
ここには非常に優れた健全なビルマのシステムがあります
Kill him as soon as your cancer cells come out
ガン細胞が出てきたらすぐに殺してください
So you don't even know, you still feel healthy
だからあなたは自分でも気づいていないのに、あなたはまだ健康だと感じています
Most people are in this state
ほとんどの人がこの状態です
But some are still sick
しかし、まだ病気の人もいます
Cancer is becoming more and more
がんはどんどん増えていく
this starts
これが始まります
Because what the IC package just said
ICパッケージが今言ったことだから
survival of the fittest
適者生存
IC package if he is not applicable in
IC パッケージが適用されない場合
who here chooses him
ここで誰が彼を選ぶのか
who is going to attack him
誰が彼を攻撃するのか
is the immune system
免疫システムです
what does he apply
彼は何を適用しますか
he has to adapt the immune system
彼は免疫システムを適応させなければならない
If he can adapt the immune system
免疫システムを適応させることができれば
It's because he's not afraid of the immune system
それは免疫システムを恐れていないからです
he has a chance to survive
彼には生き残るチャンスがある
So there are some IC packages
ICパッケージもいくつかあります
changes in his genes
彼の遺伝子の変化
His ability to attack immune cells
免疫細胞を攻撃する能力
Greater tolerance
より大きな耐性
So these few IC packages
これらのいくつかの IC パッケージ
survive
生き残る
At this time, we enter the so-called coexistence period.
このとき、いわゆる共存期に入ります。
The coexistence period is your IC package
共存期間はICパッケージです
Although in
にありますが
But you can't go too far
でも、あまり遠くに行くことはできません
You just maintain a certain amount
一定量を維持するだけです
that's good
それは良い
I obviously controlled you first
明らかに私が最初にあなたをコントロールしました
keep you out of trouble
あなたをトラブルから遠ざけます
Most likely to remain in this state
この状態が続く可能性が高い
How to destroy this balance
このバランスをどう崩すか
a balance is to say
バランスって言うのは
immune system compromised
免疫システムが損なわれている
under certain conditions
特定の条件下で病気になる
or take some immunosuppressants
または免疫抑制剤を服用するか
or other reasons for your immune system to
または免疫システムのその他の理由
Decreased immune protection
免疫防御力の低下
At this time, cancer cells have a chance to win
現時点では、がん細胞が勝つチャンスがあります
or the continued evolution of cancer cells
または癌細胞の継続的な進化
Because your immune system is going to attack him
あなたの免疫システムが彼を攻撃するからです
killed by him
彼に殺された
If he survives, he will not be afraid of you
もし彼が生き残れば、彼はあなたを恐れないでしょう
So he slowly and gradually changed
それで彼はゆっくりと徐々に変わっていきました
This process may take a year or two, maybe ten or twenty years
このプロセスには 1 年か 2 年、場合によっては 10 年か 20 年かかる場合があります
So in the end you have some cancer cells
つまり最終的にはがん細胞が存在することになります
After he's trained, he's less afraid of your immune system attacking.
訓練を受けた後は、免疫システムが攻撃することをあまり恐れなくなります。
He has the opportunity to be under the condition of immune cell attack
彼は免疫細胞の攻撃を受ける可能性がある
He was also able to grow a large tumor
彼は大きな腫瘍を成長させることもできました
This is a clinical tumor
これは臨床腫瘍です
this time you will see a doctor
今度は医者に診てもらいます
So that is
つまり、
You see those oncologists in the clinic
クリニックにいる腫瘍学者に会います
He faces very familiar problems
彼は非常に身近な問題に直面している
because all these cancer cells
なぜならこれらすべてのがん細胞は
He is already in such a state of shock
彼はすでに深いショックを受けている
i'm so scared
とても怖いです
Then the IC protection of your patient's immune system
次に、患者の免疫システムを IC で保護します。
grow out to grow out
成長して成長する
So you need immune drugs to control it
したがって、それを制御するには免疫薬が必要です
Of course it's more difficult
もちろんもっと難しいです
So this is the problem we face clinically
これが私たちが臨床的に直面している問題です
how to deal with these
これらにどう対処するか
The fighters of IC protection who have been shocked by the immune attack
免疫攻撃に衝撃を受けたIC防御の戦士たち
How to give this immune system again
この免疫システムを再び与える方法
Stronger ability to eliminate these IC protection
これらのIC保護を排除する強力な機能
This is the only way to control these
これがこれらを制御する唯一の方法です
Clinically these IC protection
臨床的にはこれらのIC保護
Then this is what I just mentioned
それから、これは私が今言ったことです
The Four Survival Ways of IC Bao
IC Baoの4つの生き残る方法
Okay, let's give some more clinical examples
さて、もう少し臨床例を挙げてみましょう
This is the treatment of colorectal cancer
大腸がんの治療法はこれです
This is not immunotherapy, this is traditional treatment
これは免疫療法ではなく、伝統的な治療法です
surgery, radiation therapy, chemotherapy
手術、放射線療法、化学療法
Then if you look at this A, B, C, D
次に、この A、B、C、D を見ると、
The four types of patients
4つのタイプの患者
A and C
AとC
You see this tumor is very small
この腫瘍は非常に小さいことがわかります
Section 08 has not yet been violated
セクション 08 はまだ違反されていません
Therefore, this is usually classified as sweeping syndrome in pathological classification.
したがって、これは通常、病理学的分類ではスイープ症候群として分類されます。
It's probably fine to cut it off
切ってもいいかもしれない
Then that patient B and D
次に患者BとD
It's red is a cancer cell
赤いのはがん細胞です
Not only in the original flavor but also violated the 08 section
オリジナルのフレーバーだけでなく、08セクションに違反しました
Then to this 08 tube
それからこの08チューブへ
So these patients are classified as
したがって、これらの患者は次のように分類されます。
This may be a pathological classification
これは病理学的な分類かもしれません
it may be more malignant
もっと悪性かもしれない
Already violated tube 08 so probably transferred
既にチューブ 08 に違反しているため、おそらく転送されています
The prognosis may be worse
予後はさらに悪くなる可能性がある
Then they counted a lot of treated cases
それから彼らは治療された症例をたくさん数えました
and then come to this conclusion
そしてこの結論に達する
Discover
発見
Originally this B
もともとこのB
B this A this patient looks like a small
B これ A この患者は小さく見えます
should be fine
大丈夫なはずです
It should be fine after recovery, but he is actually not well after recovery.
回復すれば大丈夫なはずだが、実は回復後も調子が良くない。
Then this D this patient
そうすると、この患者は
Looks like the red tumor has invaded the 08 section
赤い腫瘍が08セクションに侵入したようです
Then maybe it was transferred, of course everyone said
じゃあ、もしかしたら転移したかもしれない、もちろんみんな言いました
That, what Teacher Tang just said, once this is invaded, the metastatic cancer may be difficult to treat
タン先生が先ほどおっしゃったように、一度浸潤すると、転移性がんの治療は困難になる可能性があります。
But according to this patient, according to their statistics, this type of patient is not bad
しかし、この患者によると、彼らの統計によると、このタイプの患者は悪くないそうです
The big big difference is the yellow cells
大きな大きな違いは黄色のセルです
These are immune cells, especially T cells
これらは免疫細胞、特に T 細胞です
If this patient has a lot of 08 cells in the cancer tissue he removed
この患者が切除した癌組織に多くの 08 細胞がある場合
For example, patients C and D, no matter what treatment they receive, be it chemotherapy, radiotherapy, or surgery, they are less likely to relapse
たとえば、患者 C と D は、化学療法、放射線療法、手術など、どのような治療を受けても再発する可能性が低くなります。
But if he doesn't have these T cells, he will heal longer
しかし、もし彼がこれらのT細胞を持っていなければ、彼の治癒はさらに長くなります
This article, this is a Review Paper, which summarizes many clinical cases
この記事は、多くの臨床例をまとめた総説論文です
Put forward a statement at that time, that is to say, in addition to the classification of these pathologies
つまり、これらの病状の分類に加えて、その時点で声明を提出してください
People also take into account the classification of immunity
人々は免疫の分類も考慮に入れます
This way the prognosis for this cancer patient will be more accurate.
このようにして、このがん患者の予後はより正確になります。
This is the conclusion obtained in patients with colorectal cancer
これは結腸直腸がん患者において得られた結論です
Even other cancers were later found to have similar conclusions
他のがんでも同様の結論が得られることが後に判明しました
That is to say
つまり
Some patients have cancer because more T cells enter the lung
より多くのT細胞が肺に侵入するため、がんを患う患者もいます
This kind of patient is easier
こういう患者さんは楽ですよ
No matter what you do to treat him, it will be easier.
彼を治療するために何をしても、それは簡単になります。
next to ask
次に尋ねます
Why do these patients have more T cells
なぜこれらの患者にはT細胞が多いのか
I don't know
わからない
This is what we need to understand in our research
これが研究で理解する必要があることです
The next challenge of positive treatment is to say
積極的治療の次の課題は次のとおりです。
Why Only a Few Patients Have Better T Cells
なぜ少数の患者だけがより良いT細胞を持っているのか
if not
そうでない場合
Is there any way you can make it happen
それを実現する方法はありますか
That's what everyone said at the beginning
最初にみんなそう言ってた
we generate
私たちが生成する
He's phagocytosis, remember, phagocytosis
彼は貪食症です、覚えておいてください、貪食症です
after swallowing bacteria
細菌を飲み込んだ後
Bacterial antigens carried
運ばれる細菌抗原
presented to the T cell, which produces
T細胞に提示され、
Right, so we're actually progressing our immunology
そうです、私たちは実際に免疫学を進歩させています
We know how T cells are produced, we know that
私たちは T 細胞がどのように生成されるかを知っています。
Is there a way for us to use this knowledge to train
この知識をトレーニングに活用する方法はありますか?
This, the human immune system
これは人間の免疫システムです
Generate T cells that fight cancer
がんと戦うT細胞を生成する
The biggest difficulty is that we don't know much about our enemies
最大の難点は敵についてあまり知らないことだ
His cells are so similar to our cells
彼の細胞は私たちの細胞にとても似ています
Cancer cells, in the eyes of T cells
T細胞の目の中にあるがん細胞
It's almost the same as a normal cell
通常の細胞とほぼ同じです
his entire genetic makeup
彼の遺伝子構造全体
his protein
彼のプロテイン
almost very very similar to
ほぼ非常に非常によく似ています
So basically we don't react to him.
したがって、基本的に私たちは彼に反応しません。
So we have to find a way to stimulate
だから私たちは刺激する方法を見つけなければなりません
to cancer, especially to his tumor antigens
癌、特に腫瘍抗原に対して
professional reminder, save
プロのリマインダー、保存
then this may be now
それならこれは今かもしれない
May be applied to current immunization profiles
現在の予防接種プロファイルに適用できる可能性があります
That
それか
tumor microenvironment
腫瘍微小環境
We now see such a large tumor
今では非常に大きな腫瘍が見られます
a tumor
一個tumors
In fact, there are not only IC packets in this tumor.
実はこの腫瘍にはICパケットだけが存在するわけではありません。
it has a lot
それはたくさんあります
composition
組成
It's all about fighting the immune system
すべては免疫システムとの戦いについてです
so I call it
だから私はそれを呼びます
it this
それこの
Tumor microcircle is tumor micro environment
腫瘍微小円は腫瘍微小環境です
It is actually built by the IC package
実際にはICパッケージで構築されています
A well-balanced defense bag
バランスのとれた防御バッグ
who to defend
誰を守るべきか
defend your body's immune system
体の免疫システムを守る
like it has a chance of surviving
生き残る可能性があるような
That's swollen
あれは腫れてるよ
its mechanism
その仕組み
This is a kind
これは一種です
everyone can see
誰もが見ることができます
These gray ones are IC bags
この灰色のものはICバッグです
There are many cells in there
そこにはたくさんの細胞が存在します
Blood vessel
血管
Because the IC package grows it needs blood vessels
ICパッケージが大きくなるため血管が必要になる
supply it with nutrients and oxygen
栄養と酸素を供給する
Then you see there are many immune cells
すると、免疫細胞がたくさんあることがわかります。
There are also T cells
T細胞もあるよ
These antigen presenting cells, these
これらの抗原提示細胞、
The tumor micro environment just mentioned
先ほど述べた腫瘍の微小環境
both
両方
a lot of
たくさんの
So after you take that cancer out you give him a test
それで、そのガンを切除した後、検査を受けます
Anyway, there are a lot of immune cells in it
とにかく免疫細胞が多い
So that's weird. Is this immunity to attack cancer?
それは奇妙なことですが、この免疫は癌を攻撃するのでしょうか？
so what
だから何
he doesn't play his part
彼は自分の役割を果たしていない
It turns out that cancer just said that cancer should be able to
癌は癌ができるべきだと言ったばかりであることが判明しました
try to survive it evolve some different mechanics
いくつかの異なるメカニズムを進化させて生き残ろうとします
It actually removes those cancer cells
実際にそれらのがん細胞を除去します
Uh, these immune cells are going to attack it
ああ、これらの免疫細胞がそれを攻撃するつもりです
But once it gets to the cancer cell, he trains it
しかし、それががん細胞に到達すると、彼はそれを訓練します
Turn it from an enemy who attacked it to a good friend
攻撃してきた敵から親友に変える
So you look at these inside the tumor
腫瘍の内部を観察してください
Immune Cells
免疫細胞
In fact, it becomes an immune suppressor cell.
実際、それは免疫抑制細胞になります。
Its function is to suppress immune cells
その機能は免疫細胞を抑制することです
So it uses the hair of the son to attack the shield of the son
つまり、息子の髪の毛を使って息子の盾を攻撃するのです
It trains these immune cells, cancer cells to train these immune cells
これらの免疫細胞を訓練し、これらの免疫細胞を訓練するためにがん細胞を訓練します
make it able to deal with
対処できるようにする
Attack of the body's other immune cells
体の他の免疫細胞の攻撃
very strong
とても強い
So these we call
したがって、これらを私たちは呼びます
Inmute Suppressor Sales Immunosuppressive cells
Inmute Suppressor Sales 免疫抑制細胞
its essence is
その本質は
I just said that hematopoietic stem cells are trained
先ほど造血幹細胞が鍛えられると言いました。
These phagocytes
これらの食細胞は
But cancer cells have the ability to train it to
しかし、がん細胞にはそれを訓練する能力があります。
immunosuppressive cells
免疫抑制細胞
Then it uses a different mechanism
その後、別のメカニズムが使用されます
I wonder if any of you are interested in this?
皆さんの中にもこれに興味がある人はいるでしょうか？
Many different ABCDEFG
さまざまなABCDEFG
various mechanisms
さまざまな仕組み
to suppress it
それを抑えるために
OK
OK
That
それか
So here I will use cartoon clothes to introduce
そこでここでは漫画の服を使って紹介します
This is antigenic laminarity
これが抗原層状構造です
I just said that the phagocytic cells look like this
先ほど、貪食細胞はこんな感じだと言いました。
Then if you encounter this cancer cell
そして、このがん細胞に遭遇したら
it's the same it will eat it up
それは同じです、それを食べてしまいます
Useless after devouring
むさぼり食った後は役に立たない
instead it becomes
代わりに次のようになります
suppressor cells
サプレッサー細胞
Suppressor Suppressor Antigenic Laminar Cells
サプレッサー サプレッサー 抗原性層状細胞
It presents to T cells
T細胞に提示します
T cells become wet energy
T細胞がウェットエネルギーになる
Non-functioning air bag
機能しないエアバッグ
It's much different from just now
今までとは大きく違う
After touching bacteria, it looks like this
細菌に触れるとこんな感じ
it becomes this
これになります
very empty phagocytes
非常に空の食細胞
this won't work
これはうまくいきません
Then this is an activated air bag, this is a non-functional air bag
これが作動したエアバッグで、これが機能していないエアバッグです。
So there are different types of air bags
エアバッグにも色々な種類があるので、
White blood cells can disable your gas bag
白血球がエアバッグを無効にする可能性がある
good
良い
Now we think, what we now call the rapid development of immunotherapy
私たちは今、免疫療法の急速な発展と呼んでいるものを考えています。
Is there a way we can make these defunct air bags
これらの廃止されたエアバッグを作る方法はありますか?
restore its functionality
機能を復元する
A rejuvenated gas bag, if it can recognize cancer cells
がん細胞を認識できれば、若返ったガスバッグ
Is there a way to kill cancer cells
がん細胞を殺す方法はありますか
So this is what we know recently
これが最近わかったことです
Major advances in immunotherapy
免疫療法における大きな進歩
The answer, of course, is yes, at least for some patients.
もちろん、少なくとも一部の患者にとっては、答えは「はい」です。
Then its practice is the past few years
そして、その実践はここ数年です
Some breakthroughs, and then introduce these methods
いくつかの画期的な方法を紹介します
It has some effect, that is, it uses active immunotherapy
ある程度の効果がある、つまり能動免疫療法を使用する
I just talked about the back-kinetic and active-kinetic, that is, your body produces these T cells
バックキネティックとアクティブキネティックについてお話しました。つまり、身体はこれらの T 細胞を生成します。
But the T cells have been disabled and have no function, right?
でも、T細胞は無効化されていて、機能していませんよね？
A simple solution is fine, if I know that this T cell is very important
この T 細胞が非常に重要であることがわかっていれば、単純な解決策でも問題ありません。
Then I am like T cells that get the name of the city management and cultivate a large number of them.
そうすると私は都市管理の名をもらって大量に培養するT細胞のようなものです。
Enter after training
研修後にエントリー
This we call T cell infusion therapy
これをT細胞注入療法と呼びます
In this case, you can see that its function is to cut out the tumor
この場合、その機能は腫瘍を切除することであることがわかります。
These T cells inside, it will be cultivated in the future
このT細胞は将来培養される予定です
After being cultivated, it goes to the screening
栽培後は選別へ
Those T cells that kill cancer cells
がん細胞を殺すT細胞
These are added now, that is, the T cells can kill cancer cells
これらは現在追加されています。つまり、T 細胞はがん細胞を殺すことができます。
Then it will be cultivated in large numbers in the future
そうすれば将来的には大量に栽培されるでしょう
mass culture, of course it can be deactivated
大衆文化、もちろん無効化することができます
beat it into this ward
この病棟に押し込んでください
This we call T cell infusion therapy
これをT細胞注入療法と呼びます
It's a passive immunity
それは受動免疫です
very effective
非常に効果的
for certain cancers
特定のがんの場合
Now this we call Tumor Influent Tritin Lymphocyte
これを腫瘍影響トリチンリンパ球と呼びます
Lymphocytes in tumors
腫瘍内のリンパ球
This Cartysil
このカルティシル
This is the T cell of Chimeric Antigen Receptor
これがキメラ抗原受容体のT細胞です
These are essentially T cells
これらは本質的にT細胞です
It just makes it recognize different types of antigens
さまざまな種類の抗原を認識できるようにするだけです
Cartysil is currently very red
Cartysil は現在非常に赤いです
you see it for some cancers
一部のがんではそれが見られます
Especially the treatment rate of hematologic lymphoma and blood cancer
特に血液リンパ腫と血液がんの治療率
But the past is hard to imagine
しかし過去は想像するのが難しい
but it needs to be
しかし、そうする必要があります
every cancer patient
すべてのがん患者
To make its own Cartysil
独自の Cartysil を作成するには
So the fee will probably be considerable
そうすると手数料もかなりかかるだろうし
another big problem
もう一つの大きな問題
That is, how long will the effect last?
つまり、効果はどれくらい持続するのでしょうか？
This needs to be observed again
これは再度観察する必要があります
But these patients were not
しかし、これらの患者たちはそうではありませんでした
other treatment opportunities
他の治療の機会
Then use this T cell infusion therapy now
それでは、今すぐこの T 細胞注入療法を使用してください
can you
あなたはできる
Almost all cancer cells are under control
ほぼすべてのがん細胞が制御される
So this is a really big breakthrough
これは本当に大きな進歩です
But what about this infusion therapy?
しかし、この点滴療法はどうでしょうか？
with considerable side effects
かなりの副作用を伴う
Some of them even caused the death of the patient
中には患者を死に至らしめるものもあった
Because imagine this T cell
このT細胞を想像してみてください
hit so many activated T cells
非常に多くの活性化されたT細胞を攻撃します
Many found that it has similarities with normal cells
多くの人が正常細胞との類似性を発見しました
also affects normal cells
正常細胞にも影響を与える
affect normal cells
波及正常細胞
the inflammatory response
炎症反応
serious death of the patient
患者の重大な死
So any immune person who is effective
したがって、効果のある免疫のある人は誰でも
In fact, it will be accompanied by different degrees of side effects
実際には、さまざまな程度の副作用が伴います
immune-related side effects
免疫関連の副作用
some autoimmune diseases
いくつかの自己免疫疾患
so we have to learn
だから私たちは学ばなければなりません
How to control our immune system
私たちの免疫システムを制御する方法
let it work to its advantage
それを有利に働かせる
but avoid its disadvantages
しかし、そのデメリットは避けてください
This is one of the future for this immunotherapy
これはこの免疫療法の未来の 1 つです
place to learn
学ぶ場所
Then there's the other thing, the immune checkpoint elements.
それからもう一つ、免疫チェックポイントの要素です。
Then this hall award was founded in Taiwan
そしてこのホールアワードは台湾で創設されました
exist
存在
At that time in 2014
2014年のあの頃
Awarded to these two winners
受賞者2名に贈呈
One named James Ellison
ジェームス・エリソンという名前の人
U.S.
私たち。
because it is called
と呼ばれているので
Motojuku
本宿
in Japan
在日本
Then they invented separately
その後、彼らは別々に発明しました
Discover
発見
Two different immune checkpoint molecules
2 つの異なる免疫チェックポイント分子
One is called CTLA4
1つはCTLA4と呼ばれるものです
One is called PD1
1つはPD1と呼ばれます
How does it work?
どのように機能するのでしょうか?
I will tell you with cartoon pictures
漫画の絵でお伝えします
This T cell private T cell
このT細胞プライベートT細胞
just said just said
さっき言った 言ったばかり
ICB has various
ICBにはさまざまな
immunotherapeutic
免疫療法
one of them
それらの中の一つ
It's this immune checkpoint molecule.
それがこの免疫チェックポイント分子です。
it makes this
それはこれを作る
Well
良い
Performance such as this PDL1
このようなパフォーマンス PDL1
It will bind to the PD1 on the T cell
T細胞上のPD1に結合します。
After the combination, the TG package loses its function
結合後、TG パッケージはその機能を失います
So it's called an immune checkpoint, and that's it.
それが免疫チェックポイントと呼ばれるもので、それだけです。
Will the TG package function
TGパッケージは機能しますか
It manifests itself on the immune will cells
それは免疫意志細胞に現れます
also manifested on the returning cells
戻ってきた細胞にも現れます
So it's easy, when you understand the principle
原理を理解すれば簡単です
I just thought, what if, with this combination, I will make the TG package lose its function
ちょっと考えたのですが、この組み合わせで TG パッケージの機能を失ったらどうなるでしょうか
I'll break its bond
その絆を断ち切ってやる
So they invented these two antibody drugs
そこで彼らはこれら 2 つの抗体薬を発明しました
Inject antibody drugs into
抗体医薬品を注射する
What about antibodies, bind to it
抗体はどうですか、それに結合します
unite with it, uh, separate it
それと団結して、えー、分離して
The TG package will no longer be affected by these two molecules at this time
現時点では、TG パッケージはこれら 2 つの分子の影響を受けなくなります。
regulation of elicited immune volition
誘発された免疫意欲の調節
Then this TG package didn't seem to work
それから、このTGバッグは機能しなかったようです
seems to restore its functionality
機能が回復したようです
Is there any chance to restore the function of TG package like this?
このような TG パッケージの機能を復元する機会はありますか?
to kill the patient's tumor
患者の腫瘍を殺すために
as it is
そのまま
Principle of action
作用原理
So the patient is injected with this antibody
したがって、患者にはこの抗体が注射されます
Look at this example, these two articles are in
この例を見てください。これらの 2 つの記事は次のとおりです。
Published in well-known medical journals for 12 years
12年間にわたって有名な医学雑誌に掲載
The New England Journal
ニューイングランド・ジャーナル
introduce the story
話を紹介する
Let me give you a few examples. This is lung metastasis before treatment.
いくつか例をあげますと、これは治療前の肺転移です。
Administration This is PD1
管理 こちらはPD1です
this healing machine
この治癒機械
after 90 days
90日後
This is liver metastases
これは肝臓転移です
And then here are the T cells in the tumor before treatment
これが治療前の腫瘍内の T 細胞です
Black
黒
few
少し
after treatment you see
治療後に見ると
Breath puts a lot of increase
ブレスはかなり増加します
may restore it to function
機能を回復できるかもしれません
this is
これは
this is skin
これは皮膚です
menanoma, melanoma
黒色腫、黒色腫
Before treatment
治療前
the tumor
腫瘍
After treatment
治療後
Then I saw the large number of T cells
すると、大量のT細胞が見えました。
So it looks like the effective treatment seems to be that the T cells
ということは、効果的な治療法はT細胞のようです
It restores the function of T cells after treatment
治療後にT細胞の機能を回復します
Then compare it with chemotherapy
次に、それを化学療法と比較します
This is an antibody for NTPD1, ​​of course this is
これはNTPD1に対する抗体です、もちろんこれは
This is a relatively short experiment, probably more than a year
これは比較的短期間の実験であり、おそらく 1 年以上かかります。
to this melanin flow
このメラニンの流れに
The over-2 survival rate of this antibody
この抗体の2以上の生存率
to about 16 months
16ヶ月くらいまで
yes win this chemistry this chemotherapy
はい、この化学療法、この化学療法に勝ちましょう
but more then
しかしそれ以上に
this kind of
このたぐいの
Immunological check check acceptor molecule
免疫学的チェック アクセプター分子をチェックする
Not just effective against one type of cancer
1種類のがんにだけ効果があるわけではない
It has different effects on lung cancer melanoma
肺がん黒色腫に対してさまざまな効果があります
Kidney cancer Stomach cancer Head kidney cancer
腎臓がん 胃がん 頭部腎臓がん
have varying degrees of effect, for example, on lung cancer
肺がんなどに影響を与える程度はさまざまです
This study is 23%
この研究は23％です
23% of patients
患者の23%
Responsive
レスポンシブ
The best is black is 5% to 30%
最も良いのは黒で、5% ～ 30% です。
The other about 10%
残りは10％くらい
Don't forget that these are patients with no means of treatment in the past
過去に治療手段のなかった患者たちであることを忘れないでください
So now we can achieve a success rate that is almost close to 20%
したがって、現在ではほぼ 20% に近い成功率を達成できます。
Using such an immune test for small molecules
このような小分子に対する免疫検査の使用
What he is most concerned about is how long his curative effect can last.
彼が最も懸念しているのは、治療効果がどれくらい持続するかである。
If he only lives two years, it doesn't seem like enough.
2年しか生きられないとしても、それでは十分ではないように思えます。
you want to heal him
あなたは彼を癒したいのですか
is there any chance
チャンスはありますか
Then this clinical trial
それからこの臨床試験は
this is not a clinical trial
これは臨床試験ではありません
This is because the CTOA4 immune test was detected earlier
これはCTOA4免疫検査が早期に検出されたためです
So he's been a patient long enough now
だから彼はもう十分長い間患者だった
end up over 10 years
結局10年以上かかる
Then recently they reorganized and published the results
そして最近彼らはその結果を再編成して公表した
wait a minute
ちょっと待って
This is the more than 1000 people
こちらは1000人以上
Nearly 2,000 of these patients
そのうち約 2,000 人がこれらの患者
how to read it here
ここでどう読むか
This is over 25
これは25を超えています
his survival rate
彼の生存率
That is, if you die, he will decrease
つまり、あなたが死んだら彼は減少します
Then this is the time, from the beginning, all the patients are alive
じゃあ今度は最初から患者は全員生きてるよ
And then at one year, at 12 months, about half of the patients are still alive
そして1年後、12か月後、患者の約半数はまだ生きています。
Then these are the transferred melanin materials, which were almost difficult to treat in the past
これは、これまで治療がほとんど困難であったメラニン物質が転写されたものです。
In two years, there will be a little more than 20% left
2年後には20％強残るだろう
There are probably more than 2 out of 10 people who can survive
おそらく10人中2人以上は生き残れるだろう
But you only need to survive for two years, with this medicine for two years, it seems that it will be fine
でも2年生きればいい、この薬を2年飲めば大丈夫らしい
it just keeps dying without these
これらがなければ死んでいくだけです
Look at it for three years, four years, five years until ten years
3年、4年、5年、10年まで見てください。
but maintain this cove
でもこの入り江を維持してください
So this group of patients, the lucky ones, seems to be cured
したがって、このグループの患者、幸運な人たちは治癒したようです
So I just spoke, as if cured, over ten years
だから私はただ、10年以上もの間、まるで治ったかのように話した
will really take longer
本当にもっと時間がかかります
Can be verified but should be very organic
検証は可能ですが、非常に有機的である必要があります
even if not cured
治らなくても
Possibly, he's also been held in check by the immune system for a long time.
おそらく、彼は長い間免疫システムによって抑制されてきたのかもしれません。
So at least this is a very
したがって、少なくともこれは非常に重要です
In the field of cancer treatment is a
がん治療の分野では、
almost unheard of
ほとんど聞いたことのない
A cancer patient can live for such a long time
がん患者はこんなにも長生きできる
so many patients
とても多くの患者
If it is 1861 bit 20%
1861ビットの場合は20%
that is there
それはそこにあります
More than 300 fast 400 people
300名以上 最速400名
But it's a pretty impressive number
しかし、これはかなり印象的な数字です
If many patients
患者数が多ければ
Other cancer patients have the same effect
他のがん患者にも同様の影響がある
that is a very generous
それはとても寛大です
that looks now
それは今見えます
The effect of PD1
PD1の効果
better than this CDLF
このCDLFよりも優れています
So it has the potential to be better curative
したがって、より良い治療効果が得られる可能性があります
Is that true for other types of cancer?
それは他の種類の癌にも当てはまりますか?
It also has such a good effect
こんな良い効果もありますよ
depends on
に依存します
After that tracked treatment
その後の追跡治療
then this is me
それならこれが私です
Ask the student to sort it out
生徒に整理してもらいます
These drugs are available in Taiwan
これらの薬は台湾で入手可能です
This PD1 monoclonal antibody
このPD1モノクローナル抗体は
Pembro Zilume
ペンブロ・ジルメ
This is another PD1 antibody
これもPD1抗体です
This is the CT2F4 antibody
これがCT2F4抗体です
different name
違う名前
This word is per kilogram
この単語はキログラムあたりです
two fate monsters
二匹の運命の怪物
It is about 50 100 for a patient weighing 50 kg
体重50kgの患者の場合は約50 100です。
once every three weeks
3週間に1回
260,000 once
1回26万
so the price is very good
だから価格はとても良いです
if you play for a year
1年プレイしたら
4000000
4000000
then this drug
それならこの薬
Because it hits more frequently than
よりも頻繁にヒットするため、
see 900
900を参照
In this case, the most frequent frequency may be 300
この場合、最も頻繁な頻度は 300 になる可能性があります。
So it's expensive anyway
だからとにかく高い
And then only about 20%
そして、わずか20％程度
efficient
効率的
may also be responsible
責任もあるかもしれない
But you look like you might be called Q
でも君はQと呼ばれそうな顔してるね
It's not the same as in the past. In the past, you might extend
過去と同じではありません。以前は、延長する可能性がありました。
This may be called the global
これはグローバルと言えるかもしれません
So there is a big problem here
ここで大きな問題が発生します
How about us because it costs a lot and needs to be traded to varying degrees
コストが高く、程度の差こそあれ取引が必要となるため、当社はどうでしょうか。
This side effect, is there a way to screen out these potentially effective
この副作用ですが、これらの潜在的に効果的なものを排除する方法はありますか?
20% of the patients, then I just treat those patients
患者の 20% なら、私はそれらの患者を治療するだけです
The other 8% doesn't work anyway, so don't waste the money
残りの 8% はいずれにせよ機能しないので、お金を無駄にしないでください
So this is currently a very important research figure called BioMark
これは現在 BioMark と呼ばれる非常に重要な研究数値です
Biomarker How to find patients who may be effective
バイオマーカー 効果が期待できる患者を見つける方法
And then treat these patients, wait a minute, I just had a breakthrough last month.
そしてこれらの患者を治療します、ちょっと待ってください、私は先月画期的な進歩を遂げたばかりです。
So I'm going to make that slide again today
今日もそのスライドを作ります
And now, several challenges, expensive
そして今、いくつかの課題があり、費用がかかります
Too expensive but help
高すぎるけど助かる
And the second one, there are only a few patients left because 20% is not bad
2 つ目は、20% は悪くないので、患者はわずかしか残っていない
The price is very low, yes
価格は非常に安いです、はい
5 people only one
5人で1人だけ
But for him, his 20% is very useful
しかし彼にとって、彼の 20% は非常に役に立ちます
We have a way to develop more effective
より効果的な開発方法があります
From 20% and up
20%以上
The third is that it is inevitable that
3つ目は、それは避けられないということです。
With immune-related side effects
免疫関連の副作用がある
serious will be serious
深刻なことは深刻になるだろう
In this regard, further research and development
この点に関しては、さらなる研究開発が必要です
Next, I will tell him some of the decisions about immunotherapy.
次に、免疫療法に関するいくつかの決定を彼に伝えます。
You just saw that example
あなたはちょうどその例を見ました
patients with colorectal cancer receiving traditional treatment
従来の治療を受けている結腸直腸がん患者
If he has T cells
T細胞を持っている場合
Colorectal cancer is more likely to be better
大腸がんは良くなる可能性が高い
In fact, it was found that the immune
実際、免疫力が低下していることが分かりました。
Why in 20% of patients
患者の 20% でな​​ぜそうなるのか
who works and who doesn't
誰が働き、誰が働かないか
You see, this is a patient who doesn't respond to treatment.
ほら、これは治療に反応しない患者です。
Before treatment After treatment This is his tumor
治療前 治療後 これが彼の腫瘍です
This is to see that CDS is a kind of T cell
これは、CDS が T 細胞の一種であることを示しています。
you can't see the black one
黒いのは見えません
A little bit here, only a little bit after treatment
ここで少しだけ、治療後少しだけ
So this patient is nothing small
つまり、この患者は決して小さいものではありません
But look at the patient who was treated effectively
しかし効果的な治療を受けた患者を見てください
Some T cells were already present before treatment
一部の T 細胞は治療前にすでに存在していました
more after treatment
治療後にさらに
Then the tumor was under his control
その後、腫瘍は彼の制御下にあった
So they found that for the same reason
彼らは同じ理由でそれを発見しました
If the patient
もし患者が
He already had these T cells in
彼はすでにこれらのT細胞を持っていました
It's just that he lost the function of T cells called wet energy.
ただ、ウェットエネルギーというT細胞の機能を失ってしまったのです。
I didn't just say that
ただそう言っただけじゃない
put that brake on
そのブレーキをかけてください
Get rid of the reason that made him burn into wet energy
彼をウェットエネルギーに燃え上がらせた原因を取り除いてください
The T cells are reactivated
T細胞が再活性化される
But if you don't have this kind of T cells
しかし、この種のT細胞を持っていない場合は、
Then you don't suck
それなら、あなたは最悪ではありません
It's useless for you to take medicine now
今薬を飲んでも無駄です
you don't have
あなたは持っていません
so it's going to be a challenge
だからそれは挑戦になるだろう
how to make this patient
この患者をどうやって作るか
The original non-existing system package to fight cancer
がんと闘うための、存在しない独自のシステムパッケージ
In this way, more patients can be benefited
そうすれば、より多くの患者が恩恵を受けることができる
The other 80% of patients
残りの80％の患者さんは
This is the direction of future research and development
これが今後の研究開発の方向性です
Oh, that's what I just said
ああ、それは私が今言ったことです
It was a report that came out last month.
先月出たレポートです。
This report is actually quite an astonishing one.
この報告書は実際には非常に驚くべきものです。
What I just talked about is melanin flow
今お話ししたのはメラニンの流れについてです
Melanin flow is not so much in Taiwan
台湾はメラニンの流出が少ない
Our concern is lung cancer
私たちの懸念は肺がんです
liver cancer
肝臓がん
colorectal cancer deer cancer
大腸癌 鹿癌
These are the most common
これらが最も一般的です
Are these effective against these common cancers?
これらは一般的な癌に対して効果があるのでしょうか?
Well, they are the findings of this study
まあ、これらはこの研究の結果です
There is something we call tumor heart anticancer
私たちが腫瘍心臓抗がんと呼ぶものがあります
Called Neoantigen
ネオアンチゲンと呼ばれる
just mentioned
先ほど述べた
Cancer cells are different from normal cells
がん細胞は正常な細胞とは異なります
because it keeps mutating
変異し続けるから
Mutations are the guarantee of its survival
突然変異はその生存の保証である
It was born because of a mutation so it was able to
突然変異によって生まれたので、
Blaming itself for survival, so it keeps accumulating these different mutations
生き残るために自分自身を責めるため、さまざまな突然変異を蓄積し続ける
What about some of these mutations, which can cause tumor heart antigen
腫瘍心臓抗原を引き起こす可能性のあるこれらの変異のいくつかについてはどうですか
Then they found that some cancers
それから彼らはいくつかの癌を発見しました
Because of gene repair, our body cells have a repair function
遺伝子修復により、私たちの体の細胞は修復機能を持っています
Then when you mutate, we'll have some
そうすれば、あなたが突然変異するとき、私たちはいくつかのものを手に入れるでしょう
Some efficiencies will fix it back
いくつかの効率化により問題は元に戻ります
But some cancer cells have lost this correction function
しかし、一部のがん細胞はこの修正機能を失っています
This is a tumor where the body's genetic repair is defective
これは体の遺伝子修復に欠陥がある腫瘍です
because it cannot correct these mutations
これらの突然変異を修正できないため、
So of course it will accumulate more mutations
したがって、当然、さらに多くの突然変異が蓄積されます
tumor heart antigen
腫瘍心臓抗原
That antigen is what produces T cells
その抗原がT細胞を生み出すのです
necessary molecule
必要な分子
So the researcher thinks that if the tumor
そこで研究者は、もし腫瘍が
have more antigens
より多くの抗原を持っている
more of this
これ以上
Newtation
ニューテーション
So, will this become easier for
それで、これはもっと簡単になりますか？
You've got to work too, that's their hypothesis
あなたも働かなければならない、それが彼らの仮説です
So they are screening
それで彼らはスクリーニングを行っている
inside the tumor
腫瘍の内部
Tumors with defects in gene repair
遺伝子修復に欠陥のある腫瘍
only treat this patient
この患者だけを治療する
see if it responds better
反応が良くなるかどうかを確認してください
At this time it is not only doing
現時点では、ただやっているだけではなく、
Just now that melanoma it did across
たった今、その黒色腫がやってきた
12 different types of cancer
12種類のがん
86 patients with genetic autumn blood
遺伝的秋血症患者86人
The number of patients is not that many 86 patients
患者数はそれほど多くない 86名
This includes the most common
これには最も一般的なものが含まれます
colorectal cancer
大腸癌
This is pancreatic cancer
これは膵臓がんです
this
これ
There is still hope, there is no lung cancer here
まだ希望はある、ここには肺がんはない
this is stomach cancer
これは胃がんです
12 Different Gene Repair Defective Cancers
12 の異なる遺伝子修復欠陥がん
treatment effect
治療効果
this is
これは
belly hundred is
腹百は
Eliminate all. It originally treats those that are not eliminated as zero.
全て排除する 本来は排除されなかったものをゼロとして扱います。
The tumor turned out to be five centimeters
腫瘍は5センチだったことが判明
You are still five centimeters after treatment, that is to maintain the same
治療後もまだ 5 センチメートル、つまり同じ状態を維持することです。
it doesn't last long
それは長くは続かない
But if it becomes zero
でもそれがゼロになったら
If there is nothing, then this one is over here
何もなければ、これはここです
This is negative 100, all disappeared
これはマイナス100です、すべて消えました
From here, patients like these are
ここからは、このような患者様が
Not only is it useless after treatment, but he continues to grow
治療後は役に立たないだけでなく、成長し続けます
But as you can see, useful patients
しかし、ご覧のとおり、有用な患者は
It has reached 50%
50%に達しました
From just a few dozen, now to 50%
わずか数十から、今では 50% に
The only thing he did was to sift through those
彼がした唯一のことはそれらをふるいにかけることだった
Tumors with gene repair tangents
遺伝子修復タンジェントを持つ腫瘍
That will significantly increase his healing effect.
それは彼の治癒効果を大幅に高めるでしょう。
The longest of these has been almost three years
最長で3年近くかかりました
So tell us here, one of the
そこで、ここで教えてください、そのうちの 1 つを
effective against immune persons, that is
免疫のある人に対して効果がある、つまり
This tumor, it has many genetic mutations
この腫瘍には多くの遺伝子変異があります
Mutations in this gene create new antigens
この遺伝子の変異により新しい抗原が生成されます
new antigen
新しい抗原
May stimulate more somatic cells
より多くの体細胞を刺激する可能性があります
worked for him, so their study actually found
それは彼にとって効果があったので、彼らの研究は実際に次のことを発見しました
After treatment, these systemic cells that are specialized for tumor heart antigens were found to increase
治療後、腫瘍心臓抗原に特化したこれらの全身細胞が増加することが判明しました。
This tells the story
これは物語を物語ります
Tumors are most afraid of systemic cells
腫瘍が最も恐れるのは全身細胞です
Tumors with more genetic mutations
より多くの遺伝子変異を持つ腫瘍
Although it can apply this immune system attack
この免疫システム攻撃を適用することはできますが、
but
しかし
It is also more susceptible to systemic attack
また、全身的な攻撃を受けやすくなります
Now if say
今言うなら
Clinicians
臨床医
That's actually been approved
それは実際に承認されました
This is a treatment with a rare
珍しい治療法です
that is
あれは
It has been approved that is to say as long as
つまり、次の限り承認されています
patients with metastatic cancer
転移性がん患者
patients with gene repair tangents
遺伝子修復タンジェントを持つ患者
can be treated with this drug
この薬で治療できます
Then Taiwan should not have entered yet.
それなら台湾はまだ入っていないはずだ。
But I reckon this should be fast
しかし、これは速いはずだと思います
will be approved in Taiwan
台湾でも承認される予定
that's right
それは正しい
Many patients with metastatic cancer are of course a great boon.
もちろん、多くの転移性がん患者にとっては大きな恩恵です。
If you have cancer, it happens to be the tangent of this kind of gene repair
がんがある場合、たまたまこの種の遺伝子修復が行われる可能性があります。
then just
それからちょうど
for this immunotherapy
この免疫療法には
The success rate will be significantly improved
成功率が大幅に向上します
Then this is some basic research that can help some clinical progress
これは臨床の進歩に役立つ基礎研究です
next last little time
次の最後の少しの時間
now let's do
さあ、やってみましょう
that just said this
それはちょうどこれを言った
whether gene repair defect
遺伝子修復に欠陥があるかどうか
You actually rely on the T cells that your patient originally had.
実際には、患者が元々持っていた T 細胞に依存しています。
If the patient has no T cells
患者に T 細胞がない場合
Then you fight these current immune will machines
それからあなたはこれらの現在の免疫意志マシンと戦います
it's useless
無駄だ
but we said
でも私たちは言いました
that triggers a T cell response
T細胞反応を引き起こす
We actually have a lot of experience in the past
実は私たちには過去にたくさんの経験があります
Ability we know how to elicit a good T cell response
良好な T 細胞応答を引き出す方法を知っている能力
phagocytic activated phagocytes
食細胞によって活性化された食細胞
to present antigen
抗原を提示する
costimulatory molecule
共刺激分子
Cytokines
サイトカイン
Like this one triggers a nice T cell response
これは素晴らしいT細胞反応を引き起こします
So we are simulating
それでシミュレーションしています
works like this
このように機能します
So we use the method of doing
したがって、次の方法を使用します
radioimmunotherapy
放射線免疫療法
go find this cancer
この癌を探しに行きます
destroy it
それを破壊する
Didn't I just say that there are many cotton liquid lipid cells in it?
綿液状の脂質細胞がたくさん入っていると言いましたよね？
I can't kill tumor cells
腫瘍細胞を殺すことはできない
Also kills cotton lipocytes
綿脂肪細胞も殺します
break down his entire fortress
彼の要塞全体を破壊する
At this time, the cancer cells released
このとき、がん細胞が放出される
He will also release this tumor antigen
彼はこの腫瘍抗原も放出します
What about after his whole antigen is released?
彼の抗原全体が放出された後はどうなるでしょうか?
Then you use immune drugs to deactivate the cells
次に、免疫薬を使用して細胞を不活性化します。
Finally hope that these T cells
最後に、これらの T 細胞が
It can not only treat the cancer of the original stomach
元々の胃がんを治療するだけではありません
And he can use what he just said
そして彼は今言ったことを使うことができる
the lymphatic system blood circulatory system
リンパ系 血液循環系
to find those who hide somewhere
どこかに隠れている人たちを見つけるために
not yet visible to the naked eye
まだ肉眼では見えません
I can't see that CT yet.
CTはまだ見えません。
metastatic cancer
転移性がん
control it
それを制御する
or make peace with it
あるいはそれと和解するか
or just kill it
あるいはただ殺すだけ
This is the principle of the whole treatment
これが治療全体の原則です
we designed the animal model
私たちは動物モデルをデザインしました
Make a big factory to come to the cell
独房に来る大きな工場を作る
day zero fight
ゼロ日目の戦い
To simulate a large factory to dry transfer
大規模な工場から乾式搬送までをシミュレートするには
we hit it to this leather stick
この革の棒にぶつける
it will transfer to dry
乾燥に移行します
wait till it grows
成長するまで待ってください
about 14 days later
約14日後
This original position has been hit
この元の位置はヒットしました
more than 1 cm
1cm以上
Metastatic cancer at this time
この時点で癌は転移している
eyes can't see yet
目はまだ見えません
But in a microscope like you can see
しかし、顕微鏡で見るとわかるように、
this
これ
here
ここ
here are all these
すべてここにあります
we treat
私たちは治療します
Only treat the cancer in situ
上皮内がんのみを治療する
we only treat this
私たちはこれだけを扱います
14 days old swollen face in situ
生後14日目の顔の腫れ
Let's pretend we don't see the metastatic cancer
転移がんは見て見ぬふりをしましょう
The main purpose is to
主な目的は、
Is there a way we can treat this
これを治療する方法はありますか
carcinoma in situ
上皮内癌
Simultaneous immune response
同時免疫反応
Of course the immune cells
もちろん免疫細胞も
attack the cancer cells that have metastasized
転移したがん細胞を攻撃する
This is what we designed first
これが私たちが最初に設計したものです
Let's design a few groups
いくつかのグループをデザインしてみましょう
a group does not treat it
グループはそれを扱いません
when compared
比較すると
One group only received radiation therapy
1 つのグループは放射線療法のみを受けました
One group only received immunotherapy and cell-based therapy
1つのグループは免疫療法と細胞ベースの療法のみを受けました
The other group is radiation plus immunotherapy.
もう 1 つのグループは放射線療法と免疫療法です。
Its principle is to hope to generate new system cells
その原理は、新しいシステム細胞の生成を期待することです
This is a control for carcinoma in situ
これは上皮内癌のコントロールです
This one does not treat it from day 1 we start treatment on day 14
これは1日目から治療するのではなく、14日目から治療を開始します
At this time, it is about 100 to 200 cubic meters.
このとき、100～200立方メートル程度です。
Then when it is not treated, it continues to grow, and it grows here in 20 days
その後、治療しないと成長を続け、20日でここまで成長します
Any bigger and we'll kill
それ以上大きくなると殺します
This is cellular immunotherapy itself, radiation therapy
これは細胞免疫療法そのもの、放射線療法です
Radiation therapy alone, or immunotherapy alone, doesn't work very well.
放射線療法単独や免疫療法単独ではあまり効果がありません。
It can delay its growth but still long
成長を遅らせることはできるが、それでも長い
But if you combine these two treatments, the flow will disappear as soon as you see it
でも、この2つの施術を組み合わせると、流れがみるみるうちに消えていきます。
And not only for this transfer, but also for the transfer in the liver
そしてこの転移だけでなく、肝臓への転移も
this is no treatment
これは治療法ではありません
this is radiation therapy
これは放射線療法です
this is immunotherapy
これが免疫療法です
Although immunotherapy seems to be less effective than radiotherapy for the original taste
免疫療法は放射線療法よりも本来の味に対する効果が低いようですが
But it is better for cancer treatment and effect
でも癌には良いし効果もある
Most notably, this combined treatment
最も注目すべきは、この複合治療です
another pattern
別のパターン
Then after you treat this is no treatment
治療した後は治療ではありません
Radiation therapy is to look at the T cells
放射線療法はT細胞を調べることです
T cells in the tumor
腫瘍内の T 細胞
You can see more about this seventy-eighty-seventy treatment
この7870治療について詳しく見ることができます
Combination therapy
併用療法
secret numb
秘密のしびれ
T cell responses following treatment
治療後の T 細胞反応
Another model is the spontaneous breast cancer model
別のモデルは、自然発生乳がんモデルを使用することです。
Those modes just now used the job transfer mode
これらのモードは今ジョブ転送モードを使用していました
you inject cancer cells into
がん細胞を注射する
Then this is to let the mice produce cancer cells by themselves
次に、マウスに自分でがん細胞を生成させます。
a bit closer to human
少しは人間に近づいた
That's breast cancer
それは乳がんです
In this model, there are fifteen pairs of mice in Lu County, and ten
このモデルでは、魯県には 15 対のネズミがおり、10 対のネズミがいます。
That is in Lu County, so there are only ten in this place
その魯県なので、この元の位置には10人しかいません
Then he will transfer to waste
それから彼は廃棄物に移るでしょう
About four months will be transferred to waste
約4か月が無駄に費やされる
Then this is related to waste
それから、これは廃棄物に関係します
There are still a lot of finalists, ranking second in the world
世界第2位のファイナリストはまだたくさんいる
Then Taiwan is the fourth place, so this is no treatment
じゃあ台湾は4位だからこれは仕方ないね
Radiation plus immunotherapy, this PDL1 antibody
放射線と免疫療法、この PDL1 抗体
Immunotherapy is not the only one
免疫療法だけが治療法ではない
In our development rate of more than one hundred years, a very wide variety of immunotherapies have been developed
100年を超える開発速度の中で、非常に多種多様な免疫療法が開発されてきました。
Antibodies against PDL1 are one type of immunotherapy
PDL1 に対する抗体は免疫療法の一種です
Then our laboratory uses this cytokine immunotherapy
そこで当研究室ではこのサイトカイン免疫療法を行っています
Then this laboratory compares these two immunotherapies
次に、この研究室ではこれら 2 つの免疫療法を比較します
Effects of Concomitant Radiation Therapy
併用放射線療法の影響
Just relying on immunotherapy, in the Jiangdong mode, there is no obvious effect
免疫療法に頼るだけでは、江東モードでは明らかな効果はありません
But then combining those two treatments, it's pretty obvious
しかし、これら 2 つの治療法を組み合わせると、それは非常に明白です
The metastases to the lungs are also seen to be very obvious
肺への転移も非常に明白であることがわかります
The white ones are metastatic cells
白いのは転移細胞です
Of course, these are still in animal experiment mode.
もちろん、これらはまだ動物実験モードです。
We also recently communicated with National Taiwan University Animal Hospital
私たちは最近、国立台湾大学動物病院とも連絡を取りました。
Animals, dogs, cats, older, get cancer like that
動物、犬、猫、高齢者はガンになる
It also treats radiotherapy, chemotherapy, surgery
放射線療法、化学療法、手術も治療します
So the doctors at National Taiwan University Animal Hospital have been in contact with these patients
したがって、国立台湾大学動物病院の医師たちはこれらの患者と接触しています。
We now hope that from small animals to a spontaneous pet cancer
私たちは今、小動物から自然発生的なペットのがんまで、
get closer to humans
人間に近づく
Then, using this combination of radiation and immunization
次に、この放射線と予防接種の組み合わせを使用します。
This is our first therapy dog
初めてのセラピー犬です
Received this radiation therapy at Taipei Medical University
台北医科大学で放射線治療を受けました
Then we'll give it immunotherapy
それから免疫療法をしましょう
Then I took it to the National Taiwan University Animal Hospital for observation.
その後、観察のために国立台湾大学動物病院に連れて行きました。
Finally, this history will make a summary
最後にこの歴史を総括します
It is hoped that immunotherapy will be combined with precise treatment
免疫療法と精密治療の併用が期待される
or can eradicate cancer
あるいは癌を根絶できる
or you can coexist peacefully
あるいは平和的に共存することもできる
long-term peaceful coexistence
長期的な平和共存
this is also a cure
これも治療法です
Then I think I will introduce you to this side today
それでは今日はこの辺を紹介していこうと思います
Then use half an hour
それから30分を使います
Welcome to ask questions
ご質問を歓迎します
Well, we thank Teacher Cao Mihua for a very wonderful speech
さて、とても素晴らしいスピーチをしてくれた曹美華先生に感謝します。
let's open first
まずは開けてみましょう
please ask us
聞いてください
Before I do that, let me announce
その前に発表させてください
we have prepared scientific magazine
科学雑誌をご用意しました
event book
有事本
So I encourage you to ask questions
質問することをお勧めします
so we
だから私たちは
The first ten of us who asked the question
質問をした最初の 10 人
We'll have someone give one to a Science Man magazine
誰かに Science Man 誌に贈ってもらいましょう
good
良い
Levi
リヴァイ
ask the professor
教授に聞く
just mentioned that
ちょうどそれを言いました
that immune system
その免疫システム
And that T cell
そしてそのT細胞は
That good effect on our body
私たちの体に良い影響を与える
then i was thinking
それから私は考えていました
Prevention is better than cure
治療よりも予防​​が大切です
Then ask the professor how to live
それから教授に生き方を聞いてください
how to take care of your body
自分の体の世話をする方法
T cells can be stored in the body
T細胞は体内に保存できる
and have a good immune system
そして良好な免疫システムを持っています
Thanks
ありがとう
T cells have always been there
T細胞は常にそこにありました
how to make it more
それをさらに増やす方法
In fact, this question is actually
実はこの質問、実は
What level do you want to answer
どのレベルで答えたいですか
In fact, it is the traditional way that doctors tell you
実際、これは医師があなたに伝える伝統的な方法です。
Mom and Dad tell you about this healthy lifestyle
お父さんとお母さんがこの健康的なライフスタイルについて教えてくれます
really say that
本当にそう言う
Because Icene actually
なぜならアイスネは実際には
she doesn't look like
彼女は似ていない
Our general concept of vaccines is that you have a very clear enemy
ワクチンに関する私たちの一般的な概念は、非常に明確な敵が存在するというものです。
e.g. hepatitis B virus
例: B型肝炎ウイルス
you know what its antigen is
その抗原が何であるか知っていますか
Then I will use this antigen in advance
それでは、この抗原を事前に使用します
to elicit an immune response
免疫反応を誘発するために
But cancer didn't happen before
しかし、癌は以前には発生しなかった
you don't even know where
あなたはどこにいるのかさえ知りません
even with cancer
癌があっても
The location of its mutation is also different
変異の場所も違う
everyone may not know
誰もが知らないかもしれない
also breast cancer
乳がんも
But it has a neoantigen
ネオアンチゲン
Because there are antigens
抗原があるから
Now think every patient may be different
さて、患者はそれぞれ異なるかもしれないと考えてください
So it's not like there's a cancer vaccine
つまり、がんワクチンがあるわけではない
Everyone will basically not
みんな基本的にはしないよ
Rather, it may be that this precision
むしろこの精度なのかもしれない
for this patient
この患者のために
We need to find its tumor antigen
その腫瘍抗原を見つける必要がある
and then target this tumor antigen
そしてこの腫瘍抗原を標的にします
to create this effective immune response
この効果的な免疫反応を生み出すために
Fortunately we are now
幸いなことに私たちは今、
This software called Generational Genome Analysis
このソフトウェアはGenerational Genome Analysisと呼ばれます。
very progress
非常に進歩している
so estimate
それで見積もります
Future cancer patients their cancer cells
将来のがん患者のがん細胞
do this again
これをもう一度やってください
sequencing of sequences
配列の配列決定
Yes, the price can be very high
はい、価格は非常に高くなる可能性があります
competitive
競争力
I don't know how expensive it is
どれくらい高価なのか分かりません
But it should get cheaper
でももっと安くなるといいな
Then it's possible to find
そうすれば見つけることが可能です
this patient
この患者
The position of his mutation gene mutation
彼の突然変異の場所
Then design according to this
あとはこれに従ってデザインしてみます
The best immunotherapy for this patient
この患者にとって最適な免疫療法
As for how to go
行き方としては
to take care of cancer patients
がん患者の世話をする
that your good immunity
あなたの免疫力が良いことを
maintain a healthy life
健康的な生活を維持する
Early to bed, early to rise, no drinking, no smoking
早寝早起き、禁酒、禁酒
these sports
これらのスポーツ
these are very basic
これらは非常に基本的なものです
take care of some of the health
ある程度の健康に気を配る
deliberate act
意図的な行為
So as long as there is
だから、それがある限り
enough that
それで十分
Somatic cells and the good immune system
体細胞と良好な免疫システム
then
それから
It should definitely not be Nia.
ニアではないはずです。
no
いいえ
I just said that
私はちょうどそれを言いました
That cancer cell is actually
そのがん細胞は実は
have always existed
常に存在していた
Then you T cells to kill him
じゃあT細胞が彼を殺すんだ
Of course it will happen
もちろんそうなります
no way
とんでもない
Because we have been exposed to these natural things
私たちはこれらの自然なものにさらされているので、
Then our cells are in the process of replicating
そして私たちの細胞は複製の過程にあります
Our cells are always growing
私たちの細胞は常に成長しています
The growing process always goes wrong
成長の過程には必ず失敗がある
So there will always be errors in the process of copying
したがって、コピーのプロセスでは常にエラーが発生します
Although the number is low, it adds up to a lot
数は少ないですが、積み重なるとかなりの額になります
So there's almost no way you can say you're replicating cells
したがって、細胞を複製していると言える可能性はほとんどありません
assuming it's 100 percent correct
それが100パーセント正しいと仮定すると
there would be no cancer so to speak
いわば癌は存在しないでしょう
But that is to say, there is no such thing as 100%
しかし、つまり100%というものは存在しないのです。
That is to say, our copy is in the process
つまり、私たちのコピーは作成中です
some mutations will occur
何らかの突然変異が起こるだろう
not so accurate
あまり正確ではありません
where some mutations occur
いくつかの突然変異が発生する場所
components of cancer cells
がん細胞の成分
then some of us will attack him
そうすれば私たちの何人かが彼を攻撃するでしょう
But cancer cells have been evolving, evolving, evolving
しかし、がん細胞は進化、進化、進化し続けています
In the end he is not afraid of you
ついに彼はあなたを恐れなくなりました
So I just talked about cancer
それで、私はちょうど癌について話しました
The Four Survival Theory is just that
四生存理論はまさにそれです
So you can't say you have normal public opinion
だから正常な世論を持っているとは言えない
you won't have cancer cells
あなたにはがん細胞は存在しません
Because now cancer cells probably
なぜなら、今はおそらく癌細胞がいるからです。
Cancer counts in about five people
がんは約5人に数えられます
There's probably one of four or five people inside
おそらく中には4人か5人のうちの1人がいるだろう
So he's great
だから彼は素晴らしいんだよ
The enemies you have to deal with are powerful
対処しなければならない敵は強力です
there is one over there
あそこに1つあります
right
右
please
お願いします
teacher ask
先生が尋ねる
Just now the teacher talked about the base part
先ほど先生がベースの部分についてお話しました
Does that mean people with immune diseases
それは免疫疾患のある人を意味しますか？
less likely to get cancer
がんになる可能性が低くなります
Let's say you have erythroid cystic bowel
あなたが赤血球性嚢胞性腸を患っているとしましょう
less likely to get breast cancer
乳がんになる可能性が低くなります
This is a question with two sides
これは二面性のある質問です
I think your question is like a scientist
あなたの質問は科学者っぽいと思います
right
右
You don't know what you're doing
あなたは自分が何をしているのか分かりません
Actually because
実は、なぜなら
cancer
癌
I'm really not sure
本当にわかりません
Have read the literature on this
これに関する文献を読んだことがあります
But I'm doing hepatitis virus myself
でも肝炎ウイルスは自分でやる
he really did report
彼は本当に報告した
some immune patients
一部の免疫患者
Hepatitis Virus
肝炎ウイルス
In fact, body immunity
実は体の免疫力は
He's more of an overactive immune system
彼はこれらの免疫システムが過剰に活動している
then it looks like
そうすると次のようになります
for some infectious diseases
一部の感染症に関しては
that's right
それは正しい
chronic infectious disease
慢性感染症
So I think it's possible
だからそれは可能だと思う
but i'm not sure
確信はないけど
has anyone done it
誰かやったことがありますか
one like this
このようなもの
A large-scale statistical analysis
大規模な統計分析
I think this is in public health
これは公衆衛生上の問題だと思う
This is a possible research topic
これは可能性のある研究テーマです
font immune patient
フォント免疫患者
is it his cancer
それは彼の癌ですか
or certain cancers
または特定のがん
The attack rate will be lower
攻撃率が下がります
I think it is theoretically possible
理論的には可能だと思う
I just had two questions over there.
そこで 2 つ質問がありました。
Did it just come here?
ここに来たばかりですか？
OK, so is it?
はい、そうですか？
thank you
ありがとう
one thing yes please
一つ、はい、お願いします
Interesting Topics for Chinese Speech
中国語スピーチの興味深いトピック
What I want to ask is that it is mentioned that
私が聞きたいのは、次のように述べられているということです
is the total number of T cells
T細胞の総数です
affect the effectiveness of the entire treatment
治療全体の有効性に影響を与える
The total number of T cells
T細胞の総数
different types of T cells
さまざまな種類のT細胞
Or it is said that it is Satutoxic T cell
あるいは飽和毒性T細胞とも言われています
Or Suppressor T cell
あるいはサプレッサーT細胞
Regulatory T cell
制御性T細胞
Is there any Specific T cell?
特異的 T 細胞は存在しますか?
or total
または合計
ok then back to this
さて、それではこれに戻ります
I may have just misdefined
ただ定義を間違えただけかもしれない
T cell hormone is the T cell hormone in the seed stream
T 細胞ホルモンはシードストリーム内の T 細胞ホルモンです
in the blood that doesn't count
数えられない血の中で
In the blood, don't you only deal with the blood?
血液では血液だけを扱っているのではありませんか？
You still have to deal with these dimensional creatures, these creatures
あなたはまだこれらの次元の生き物、これらの生き物に対処しなければなりません
So our body's T cells are not just to deal with the flow
つまり、私たちの体のT細胞は流れに対処するだけではありません
Then the T cell hormones we are talking about are
次に、私たちが話しているT細胞ホルモンは次のとおりです。
T cell seed
T細胞シード
Because this T cell will go to the seed stream
この T 細胞はシードストリームに行くため
It is probably the flow of knowledge
それはおそらく知識の流れです
So what kind of T cells are more effective?
では、どのような種類の T 細胞がより効果的でしょうか?
Because T cells have a type called
T細胞には と呼ばれる種類があるため、
You just mentioned that they are heterozygous T cells
先ほどヘテロ接合性 T 細胞であるとおっしゃいましたね
Regulate T cells this is bad
T細胞を調節する、これは悪いことです
So there is Correlation
つまり相関関係がある
If we say that there are many different types of T cells
このタイプのT細胞が多ければ
In fact, the prognosis for it is relatively bad.
実際、その予後は比較的悪いです。
Icva is afraid of Cd8 T cells
IcvaはCd8 T細胞を恐れています
So it should be more and more Cd8T cells
つまり、Cd8T細胞がどんどん増えていくはずです
its prognosis
その予後
Overall prognosis will be better
全体的な予後は良くなります
that gentleman
あの紳士
professor please
教授お願いします
That's because there is a Dr. Zhuang
それは荘博士がいるからだ。
The last issue was to coexist with cancer
最後の課題はがんとの共存でした
It's after the invention of that towel fuck
それはタオルファックが発明された後のことです
Use that energy to be in touch with the heavens and the earth to coexist with cancer
そのエネルギーで天地と触れ合い、がんと共存する
That is to say
つまり
Will its activity just increase that kind of
その活動はそのようなものを増やすだけですか？
increased immune system
免疫システムの増加
In this case, if we promote everyone to exercise
この場合、全員が運動を推進すると、
It is less likely to say that cancer arises
がんが発生する可能性は低い
Do you have any research on this?
これについて何か研究はありますか？
Ladies and gentlemen, I can only talk about a healthy lifestyle.
皆さん、私は健康的なライフスタイルについてしか話すことができません。
What you said just now should actually be a kind of exercise.
今あなたが言ったことは、実際には一種の訓練になるはずです。
When you exercise as a whole, it is more important to your overall physical condition
全体的に運動する場合、全体的な体調がより重要になります。
The whole of this includes the immune system
これには免疫システムも含まれます
It should be healthier
より健康的になるはずです
But is it because of this that you don't get cancer?
でも、そのせいでガンにならないのでしょうか？
This is difficult to go, it should be in nature
ここは行くのが難しい、自然の中にあるべきだ
In science, no correlation like this has been studied
科学では、このような相関関係は研究されていません
Some people you can see some people you can see in the packing yard
梱包ヤードで見える人もいる
Life is very healthy now, long-distance running, triathlon, non-smoking
今の生活はとても健康で、長距離ランニング、トライアスロン、禁煙です。
This is the proof
これがその証拠です
So that is to say, because IC8 appeared in the evolution process
つまり進化の過程でIC8が登場したからです
Sometimes your physical condition does not mean that you are immune
体調が悪いからといって免疫があるとは限らない場合があります
So this part is hard to talk about
したがって、この部分については話しにくいです
But, overall, as long as you maintain a healthy lifestyle
しかし、全体的には、健康的なライフスタイルを維持している限り、
must be helpful
必ず役立つはずです
For example, some cancer-causing factors are known, such as obesity
たとえば、肥満などのいくつかの発がん因子が知られています。
This inflammatory response, these are all bad
この炎症反応、全部悪いんです
this is a danger signal
これは危険信号です
So if you say that the factors that can reduce the risk of these cancers
では、これらのがんのリスクを軽減できる要因は何かというと、
Then your overall VL ratio will drop, this is known
その後、全体的な VL 比率が低下することが知られています。
For example, like our carriers of hepatitis B virus
たとえば、B型肝炎ウイルスの保因者のように
If you can take medicine to control the number of hepatitis B virus
B型肝炎ウイルスの数を抑える薬を服用できる場合
that will reduce
それは減らすだろう
At least you get liver cancer rates
少なくとも肝臓がんの発生率はわかります
know this
これを知っています
there are two over there i think
あそこに2つあると思います
Mr. Levi that
それはリヴァイさん
Hello Professor
こんにちは教授
The question I want to ask is to say
私が聞きたい質問はこう言います
It was mentioned just now, in fact, it was mentioned at the beginning
先ほども言いましたが、実は最初にも言いました
our immune system
私たちの免疫システム
In fact, there are many different types of immune cells
実は免疫細胞にはさまざまな種類があり、
Contains GCC cells B cells and T cells
GCC細胞、B細胞およびT細胞を含む
Today's is what the professor just mentioned
今日は先ほど先生がおっしゃったことです
The main part of immunotherapy
免疫療法の主要部分
The feeling is to focus on the part of T cells
T細胞の部分に焦点を当てた感じ
Then in immunotherapy
その後は免疫療法で
Does it target B cells
B細胞をターゲットにするのか
Or related functions of GCC cells
または GCC 細胞の関連機能
other research done
他の研究が行われた
Thanks
ありがとう
That is, the immune system, in addition to T cells
つまり、T細胞に加えて免疫系も
Are other cells
他の細胞ですか
T cells do not activate themselves
T細胞は自ら活性化しない
right
右
It requires antigen presenting cells
抗原提示細胞が必要です
it will be alive
それは生きているだろう
so the immune system it's not
つまり免疫システムはそうではありません
can exist independently
独立して存在できる
It's actually B cells that have a very tight
実は、非常に緊密な状態にあるのはB細胞です。
regulatory relationship
規制関係
The function of B cells
B細胞の働き
Antibodies
主にベアラー抗体
Antibody
抗体
We now especially synthetically affirm
私たちは今、特に総合的に肯定します
for microbial vaccines
微生物ワクチン用
it plays a big part
それは大きな役割を果たします
this microbe
この微生物
It would have been by invading the cells of the body
それは体の細胞に侵入したことによるものでしょう
into this cell
この細胞に
Then achieve the purpose of infection
その後、感染の目的を達成します
Then if there are antibodies
それで抗体があれば
synthesize it
それを合成する
That virus can't get in
そのウイルスは侵入できない
But the antibody has to go directly
しかし、抗体は直接行かなければなりません
It also does not directly kill cancer cells
また、がん細胞を直接殺すわけではありません
What it does is probably
それが行うことはおそらく
It binds cancer cells by
それはがん細胞に結合します。
then deactivate
その後、非アクティブ化します
For example, NK cells
例えば、NK細胞
activate the phagocytic cells
食細胞を活性化する
is possible by means of something like this
このような方法で可能です
to achieve the effect of cancer control
がんを抑制する効果を得るには
But at least for now
しかし、少なくとも今のところは
That is to say, in this whole cancer immunotherapy
つまり、このがん免疫療法全体において、
In the current experience like this
このような現在の経験では
The role of T cells
T細胞が果たす役割
cellular immunity
細胞性免疫
more important role
もっと重要な役割
from animal experiments
動物実験から
Follow the end of these cancer diseases in humans
人類におけるこれらの癌疾患の終焉を追跡する
looks like this
このように見えます
So now immunotherapy
そこで今回は免疫療法
In fact, the general research focus is on
実際、一般的な研究の焦点は次のとおりです。
How to strengthen the patient's
患者の心を強くする方法
professional system fort
プロフェッショナルシステムフォート
That must be my fault
それは私のせいに違いない
it's useless
無駄だ
but relatively speaking
しかし相対的に言えば
Your role may be more prominent in the system
あなたの役割はシステム内でより目立つかもしれません
that lady is in front
あの女性は目の前にいる
right
右
Hello, teacher
こんにちは先生
I just heard more
さらに聞きました
Related to immuno checkpoint
免疫チェックポイント関連
For example, for CARTE
例えばカルテの場合
technology like this
このような技術
Is it still in clinical trials
まだ臨床試験中ですか
or already in some countries
あるいはすでに一部の国では
can be used to execute
実行するために使用できます
already on sale
すでに発売中
That Novatis
あのノヴァティス
should
したほうがいい
This is already listed
これはすでにリストされています
This is the product that can be bought
購入できる商品はこちらです
But something like this
でも、こんなことも
Every patient has to do its own CARTE sales
すべての患者は独自の CARTE 販売を行う必要があります
So the second question I want to ask is to say
それで、私が聞きたい2番目の質問はこう言います
So if we want to treat with CARTE
したがって、CARTEで治療したい場合は、
how long will it take
どのくらい時間がかかりますか
will be wrong
間違っているだろう
enough T cells
十分なT細胞
Is it possible that this T cell came from a
このT細胞が由来である可能性はありますか？
extreme blood or other
極度の血またはその他
is used
使用されている
STEM cell and then go to Differentiate to enough T cell
STEM 細胞を作成し、十分な T 細胞に分化させます。
If you hit someone's body, you must still
誰かの体を殴った場合でも、
Should be difficult from STEM cell
STEMセルからは難しいはず
Because the STEM cell just mentioned is the one
なぜなら、今述べたSTEM細胞がそれであるからです。
hematopoietic cells
造血母細胞
it differentiates a lot
それは大きく違います
You want to divide it has a mature T cell
分裂したいのは成熟したT細胞です
It's not easy
簡単ではない
So usually the patient's own
したがって、通常は患者自身のものです
mature T cells
成熟したT細胞
remodel it
それを改造する
But if I've found out that I have cancer
でももし自分が癌だとわかったら
Then I still have time to go
それならまだ行く時間はあるよ
Store enough T cells
十分な量の T 細胞を保存する
Do you want to do the next Carty?
次のカーティもやりたいですか？
or i might
あるいは私はそうかもしれない
for example
例えば
How much is best to have every year
毎年どのくらい持つのがベストか
enough stock
十分な在庫
Will be a Carty cell in the future
将来はカーティセルになります
there is no way to do it like
のようにする方法はありません
usually i
通常私は
Because of Carty cell
カーティセルのせいで
I didn't say it myself
自分で言ったわけではない
Because I am a mouse myself
私自身がネズミなので
so many are
とてもたくさんあります
purple ice pop
紫のアイスポップ
But you'll be exposed to information like this
でも、こういう情報にさらされることになる
Cartysales me
カーティセールス私
I
私
I ran into a graduate student from our biomedical institute about a few weeks ago
数週間ほど前、私たちの生物医学研究所の大学院生に会いました。
Then he is in this company now
それから彼は今この会社にいる
So called Cartysales
いわゆるカーティセール
Then I had a lot of ideas in the past
それから、私は過去にたくさんのアイデアを持っていました
I thought it was okay to ask this lady if it was done
この女性に終わったかどうか聞いても大丈夫だと思った
may take a long time
長い時間がかかるかもしれない
But they are in that company now
でも彼らは今その会社にいる
He told me about two to three weeks
2～3週間くらいだと言われました
They can make this patient's Cartysales
彼らはこの患者のカルティセールを行うことができます
he's so handsome
彼はとてもハンサムです
That is to say, it is actually very competitive.
つまり、実は競争率が非常に高いのです。
But there is still no way to solve the problem that is
しかし、問題を解決する方法はまだありません
Every patient has to do his own Cartysales
すべての患者は自分自身のカルティセールを行う必要があります
How to prepare this Cartysales
このカーティセールの作り方
how to deactivate
無効化する方法
Then how to save
ではどうやって保存するのか
These will be some of the challenges in manufacturing
これらは製造における課題の一部です
then you can imagine
それから想像してみてください
His price will be higher than the one I just put on
彼の価格は私が今着たものよりも高くなるでしょう
more, because after that drug was made
さらに、その後にその薬が作られたからです
Everyone can use it, every cancer patient can
誰もが使用でき、すべてのがん患者も使用できます
The first time you see it, only you can use it
初めて見たときはあなただけが使用できます
There are four prices, I believe it will not be cheap
価格は4つありますが、安くはないと思います
so if i already have cancer
それで、もし私がすでに癌を患っていたら
can i still have time
まだ時間はありますか
Now the most effective treatment is for blood cancer patients.
現在、最も効果的な治療法は血液がん患者に対するものです。
If you get a blood cancer patient
血液がん患者になったら
Especially a species called CD19
特にCD19と呼ばれる種
related B cell blood cancer
関連するB細胞血液がん
The cure rate is very high
治癒率が非常に高い
here, this bit, yes
ここ、このビット、はい
Then sit in the back seat over there
じゃあそこの後部座席に座ってください
come here first
まずここに来てください
hello professor, thank you for your presentation
こんにちは、教授、プレゼンテーションありがとうございました
I have two questions, the first one is
質問が 2 つあります。1 つ目は、
According to T-cell receptor
T細胞受容体によると
It is in Encode T-cell receptor
Encode T細胞受容体にあります
Is to use VDGA recombination
VDGA再結合を使用することです
so fearadically the repertoire
恐ろしいほどのレパートリー
of the T-cell detection would be
T 細胞の検出率は次のようになります。
If you can detect different energies, there will be a lot of people playing
さまざまなエネルギーを検出できれば、たくさんの人が遊ぶでしょう
Is there any related research to find out which T-cell in your body can contain Detect Cancer like Service Market
体内のどの T 細胞に含まれる可能性があるかを調べるための関連研究はありますか サービス市場のようながんの検出
The total rate of T-cell is very high, it is generated by this Recombination
T細胞の合計率は非常に高く、この組換えによって生成されます。
It recognizes a lot of antigens, so you just know its sequence is useless
多くの抗原を認識するため、その配列が役に立たないことがわかります。
You know its Sequence, but you don’t actually know what this T-cell knows.
その配列は知っていますが、実際にはこの T 細胞が何を知っているのかはわかりません。
So now it's the other way around, you first find its mutation
つまり今は逆で、まずその突然変異を見つけます。
Because T-cell recognition is these Mutation Antigen
T細胞の認識はこれらの変異抗原であるため
Then you use the so-called Neo Antigen of this Mutation
次に、この変異のいわゆる Neo Antigen を使用します。
Go see if you can stimulate the concept of T-cell, assuming that this Neo Antigen can stimulate the patient's T-cell
このネオアンチゲンが患者の T 細胞を刺激できると仮定して、T 細胞の概念を刺激できるかどうかを確認してください。
It is resistance, copy, and then see the sequence of a certain group of system packages, T-cell receptor, it really increases, then you know that this T-cell should know this neo-antigen, but the other way around
それは耐性であり、コピーし、システムパッケージの特定のグループ、T細胞受容体の配列を見て、それが実際に増加すると、このT細胞がこのネオ抗原を知っているはずであることがわかりますが、その逆です。
Another question is that your laboratory has research on combination of therapies, first you use the radiation to induce destruction of determining microenvironment, and then followed by introduction of T-cells,
もう一つの質問は、あなたの研究室では治療法の組み合わせに関する研究を行っているということです。最初に放射線を使用して決定的な微小環境の破壊を誘導し、次にT細胞を導入します。
You can talk to us on camera, I can't hear you
カメラの前で話してもいいですが、聞こえません
OK, so this question is to say, as I just said,
さて、この質問はつまり、先ほど言ったように、
For example, tumors are afraid of T-cell
たとえば、腫瘍は T 細胞を恐れます。
It's good if there are T-cells in the tumor recently
最近腫瘍にT細胞があれば良いのですが
Because yours may be more responsive
あなたのほうが反応が早いかもしれないから
So the problem just now is that my lab is doing
それで、今の問題は、私の研究室がやっていることです
radiation therapy first
まずは放射線治療
followed by immunotherapy
その後免疫療法を行う
After radiation therapy
放射線治療後
The T-cells in the tumor were killed
腫瘍内のT細胞が死滅した
that's right
それは正しい
But where does the T-cell come from?
しかし、T細胞はどこから来たのでしょうか?
come on those questions
さあ、その質問に来てください
Where is the T-cell confirmed?
T細胞はどこで確認されますか?
do not forget
忘れてはいけない
It's our body's immune system
それは私たちの体の免疫システムです
in the bone marrow
骨髄の中で
bone marrow modeling blast
骨髄モデリングブラスト
It keeps making T-cell out
T細胞を作り続けます
only when there is a tumor
腫瘍がある場合のみ
As soon as your T-cell is attracted to the tumor
T細胞が腫瘍に引き寄せられるとすぐに
It becomes an inhibitory T-cell
抑制性T細胞になる
it loses function
機能を失います
Then if we use radiation
じゃあ放射線を使うと
destroy it this tumor for the environment
環境のためにこの腫瘍を破壊してください
destroy its inhibiting environment
阻害する環境を破壊する
break down its fortress
その要塞を破壊する
In this way, you are in the newly generated T-cell
このようにして、あなたは新しく生成されたT細胞の中にいます
it has a chance
それはチャンスがある
will generate a
を生成します
effective aggressive
効果的な攻撃的な
A functional system is packaged out
機能的なシステムがパッケージ化されている
It's all about our principles
すべては私たちの原則にかかっています
that is
あれは
It's like breaking cancer into chains
それは癌を鎖に壊すようなものです
Use the square ray to knock it out first
スクエア光線を使って最初に倒しましょう
After destroying its entire environment
環境全体を破壊した後
becomes an inflamed environment
炎症を起こしやすい環境になる
At this time it is beneficial
この時期に有利なのは
immune response
免疫反応
immune response triggered like bacteria
細菌のように免疫反応が引き起こされる
Because if cancer is like bacteria
なぜなら、がんが細菌のようなものだとしたら、
to elicit such a strong immune response
このような強力な免疫反応を引き起こすには
Then we probably won't be afraid of cancer
そうすれば癌も怖くなくなるかもしれない
It is mostly after cancer cells
それは主に癌細胞の後です
It's too much like we can system package
システムパッケージ化できるのと似ている
less likely to produce a severe inflammation
重度の炎症を引き起こす可能性が低い
So you try it out on a T-shirt
それでTシャツで試してみてください
less functional
機能性が低い
But our T-shirt has always existed
でも私たちのTシャツはずっと存在していました
You know it takes care of your immune type
あなたの免疫タイプをケアしてくれるのはご存知でしょう
The soundness of hematopoietic organs
造血器の健康
you will always provide these
あなたは常にこれらを提供します
Normal T-Shirt comes out
ノーマルTシャツが登場
Mr. Mina
Mina先生
Hello, Professor, I am Jianfu
こんにちは、教授、私はJianfuです。
I'm glad you went deep into the future and talked about it in such detail.
未来のことまで詳しく話してくれて嬉しかったです。
Molecular In-Depth Physician
分子の詳細な医師
also our teacher
私たちの先生も
I think the professor just mentioned that
先ほど教授がおっしゃったと思いますが、
Play that BDL at the beginning
その BDL を最初から再生します
There is MuseoField going to eat bacteria
バクテリアを食べるミューゼオフィールドがあります
but he
でも彼は
He will have MuseoField
彼はMuseoFieldを持つことになる
but he should be
しかし彼はそうあるべきだ
because he is doing cancer
彼は癌を患っているから
he has been providing
彼が提供してくれている
MuseoField
ミュージアムフィールド
In the whole process, the structure of the RVC next to it also becomes Cancel sale
全体のプロセスで、隣の RVC の構造も販売キャンセルになります。
Even red blood cells that become polar cells start to change in shape
極細胞となる赤血球も形を変え始める
It's in the process of chasing some of our MACO jurisprudence or some
私たちの MACO 判例の一部を追跡している最中です。
Will the lost fee release some H2O2 to chase
失われた手数料は追跡するためにいくらかのH2O2を放出しますか
Or an RVC change that caused its modulus
または、その弾性率を引き起こした RVC の変更
Then after this change in the RVC of the polar cell it becomes like that
次に、極細胞の RVC がこのように変化すると、次のようになります。
Does the blood flow that helps us maintain our blood vessels become slower
血管を維持するための血流が遅くなりますか?
But some MACO jurisprudence has a chance to get where it wants to go
しかし、一部の MACO 法学には目的地に到達するチャンスがある
Because the velocity can be slower
速度が遅くなる可能性があるため、
Is that in turn a chance for us
それは逆に私たちにとってチャンスですか？
Like the teacher you just mentioned a good model
先ほど先生が良いモデルについて言及したように
It's after Redaction, which stimulates immunity to the storm
嵐に対する免疫を刺激する編集後のものです
make that place a structure
その場所を構造物にする
Attract other new TC packs
他の新しい TC パックを誘致する
Then we will evaluate it later
それでは後ほど評価させていただきます
Check whether the treatment or operating treatment is effective
治療や手術治療が効果的かどうかを確認する
Do we have a chance to look at local nearby RBC cells
近くの局所的な赤血球細胞を観察する機会はありますか?
Originally the plane of Guanghua's outer sphere
元々は光華の外圏の平面でした
It has become some acute cells or extremely strong protrusions
いくつかの急性細胞または非常に強い突起になっている
Its proportions can also become a pathological one
そのプロポーションは病的なものになることもあります
A reference to the early stages of an effective response
効果的な対応の初期段階についての言及
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you for your careful observation
注意深く観察していただきありがとうございます
In fact, I played this video for so long
実際、私はこのビデオを非常に長い間再生しました
I never went to see that RBC
私はその赤血球を見に行ったことはありません
Is there something you just said about the RBC shape change and so on
赤血球の形状の変化などについて今おっしゃったことはありますか？
I just said I really didn't pay attention
本当に気にしてなかったって言っただけだよ
Because this is from a published magazine
雑誌掲載のものなので
to expose it
それを暴露する
the object of its study
その研究の対象
It's what I just said, it sees bacteria
先ほど言った通り、細菌が見えます
See the neutral white blood cells in this city
この街の中性白血球を見てください
A lot of these optical things sometimes suffer a bit
これらの光学的なものの多くは、時々多少の影響を受けることがあります
But I guess it whole research doesn't mention this RBC
でも、研究全体ではこの赤血球については言及されていないと思います
to know me
私を知るために
What about RBC? I can't say it has no impact.
赤血球はどうですか? 影響がないとは言えません。
Because many scientists are more conservative
多くの科学者は保守的だから
If you don't know, just say you don't know
分からないなら分からないと言ってください
So RBC did not say that it is in immunotherapy
つまり、RBCは免疫療法中であるとは言っていない
Now I know what kind of role to play
どのような役割を果たせばよいのかが分かりました
currently no
現在はいいえ
As for whether he will affect immunotherapy
免疫療法に影響があるかどうかについて
He can also know by being a medium
霊媒であることで、彼も知ることができる
The effect of immunotherapy
免疫療法の効果
There is no such related report either
そのような関連報告もありません
Because basically the peritch compound H2O2
基本的にペリッチ化合物 H2O2 であるため、
After getting around by our MACOFARG or MUCOFIL
MACOFARG または MUCOFIL で移動した後
Maybe to our RBC's CELL MEMBER
たぶん私たちのRBCのCELLメンバーに
will cause a change in the structure
構造に変化をもたらすことになる
so maybe it will be a reference
なので参考になるかも知れません
That is to say, if like MUCOFIL, MACOFIL
つまり、ムコフィルのようなものであれば、マコフィル
These phagocytes
これらの食細胞は
The principle of its activation is as you just mentioned
その作動原理は今おっしゃったとおりです。
perpruritics or some other
発疹薬または他のもの
Like NL, this is called heterooxidized egg
NLと同じくヘテロ酸化卵と呼ばれます
or other principles of these bactericidal phagocytes
またはこれらの殺菌性食細胞の他の原理
may cause damage to some organizations
一部の組織に損害を与える可能性がある
So where we are speaking
それで、私たちが話しているところでは
In fact, some tissue damage will be seen
実際には、いくつかの組織損傷が見られます
need to fix later
後で修正する必要がある
It was also mentioned that
それらも言及されています
These are likely to
これらはおそらく
Cancer cells have a similar ability to attack
がん細胞も同様の攻撃能力を持っています
But this role he plays is complicated
しかし、彼が演じるこの役割は複雑です
Because you just saw his immunotherapy cells
なぜなら、彼の免疫療法細胞を見たばかりだからです
Many of these phagocytes
これらの食細胞の多くは
He called this phagocyte
彼はこの細胞を食細胞と呼んだ
cancer cells called him
ガン細胞が彼を呼んだ
All his beliefs became his
彼の信念はすべて彼のものになった
that
それか
defense force
防衛隊
So he is helping the cancer cells
つまり彼はガン細胞を助けているのです
It's more active now
今はもっと活発になってるよ
Those inside those cancer cells
がん細胞の中にいる人たち
phagocyte
食細胞
We no longer call him Phagocyte
私たちはもう彼を貪食細胞とは呼びません
we are called
私たちは呼ばれています
Immunotherapy
免疫治細胞
Most of his roles are to help cancer cells
彼の役割は主に癌細胞を助けることです
instead of killing cancer cells
がん細胞を殺す代わりに
More evidence now
今すぐさらなる証拠を
But there are also special reports that say
しかし、次のような特別なレポートもあります。
He also seems to have the ability to kill cancer cells
ガン細胞を殺す能力もあるらしい
thank you very much thank you
ありがとう、ありがとう
in the middle
中間有
right
右
we usually say
私たちは通常言います
You shouldn't be sick if you eat all you can
食べられるだけ食べれば病気にならないはず
that is our immune cells
それが私たちの免疫細胞です
The system is affected by some TRIGGER
システムは何らかのトリガーの影響を受けています
So the immune system is getting stronger
それで免疫力が強くなる
That Uncertain this natural thing
不確かなこの自然なこと
is it possible for him
彼にそれは可能ですか
That is, we are all afraid of things that come from us.
つまり、私たちは皆、自分から来るものを恐れているのです。
But is it possible for him
しかし、彼にそれは可能でしょうか
On the contrary, it will strengthen
逆に強くなるよ
our immune system
私たちの免疫システム
under certain critical conditions
特定の危機的な状況下では
Then there is another question, that is
それから、別の質問があります。
It was mentioned at the beginning
冒頭でも触れましたが
severe inflammatory reaction
重度の炎症反応
last cancer cell
最後癌細胞
Severe cancer cells are eliminated
重篤ながん細胞は除去されます
But now there is more and more evidence that
しかし今では、次のような証拠がますます増えています。
Inflammation is linked to many cancers
炎症は多くのがんと関連している
So this severe inflammation is
つまり、この重度の炎症は
On the contrary, it can miraculously cure cancer
それどころか、癌を奇跡的に治すことができる
that in chronic inflammation
慢性炎症の場合
On the contrary, it is related to many cancers
それどころか、多くのがんと関係がある
So what is the rationale for this?
では、その根拠は何でしょうか?
explain it
説明する
basically two questions
基本的に2つの質問
One is what trains cancer
1つは癌を訓練するものです
Cancer is not liver or tendon
がんは肝臓や腱ではありません
In fact, not liver or tendon
実際には肝臓や腱ではありません
Probably Vitality
おそらくバイタリティ
So in our physical environment
したがって、私たちの物理的環境では
training with what you eat
食べたものでトレーニングする
Now there are a lot of beauties who have problems
今、問題を抱えている美しい人がたくさんいます
Bacteriology, that is, our human body
細菌学、つまり私たち人間の体
It's not just human cells
人間の細胞だけではない
If you look at the skin, look at the gut
皮膚を見たら腸を見ろ
There's a lot of bacteria, a lot of microbes
細菌や微生物がたくさんいる
that some research is now very clear
いくつかの研究が現在非常に明確になっているということ
It's you who put the mouse
マウスを置いたのはあなたです
kept in a sterile environment
無菌環境で保管されている
keep it free of bacteria
細菌が入らないように保つ
This mouse's immune system is unhealthy
このマウスの免疫システムは不健康です
It was even found that
ということも判明した
Cancer in these bacteria-free mice
無菌マウスのがん
Your immune system treatment is useless
免疫システムを使って治療することはできません
So bacteria to some extent
なので、ある程度の細菌は
Humans need symbiotic bacteria with humans
人間には人間と共生する細菌が必要だ
This is called symbiotic bacteria
これを共生細菌といいます
It promotes the development of your immune system
免疫システムの発達を促進します
so this is there
それでこれはそこにあります
But Uncogean these chemical carcinogens
しかし、これらの化学発がん物質はウンコジーンです
Probably not the concept
たぶんそういう概念はない
Chemical carcinogens are these chemicals
化学発がん物質はこれらの化学物質です
Its main working principle
その主な動作原理
It's what triggers you to mutate
それが変異のきっかけになるんだよ
Increase the mutation rate, such as UV radiation, chemical substances
紫外線、化学物質などの突然変異率の上昇
The higher your mutation rate, the greater the chance of normal bubbles turning into bubbles
突然変異率が高いほど、通常のバブルがバブルに変わる可能性が高くなります
So this has nothing to do with immunity, but it is the reason why Tumor generates the entire tumor bubble
したがって、これは免疫とは関係ありませんが、腫瘍が腫瘍バブル全体を生成する理由です。
As for the second question, you can remind me again
2 番目の質問については、もう一度思い出していただけますか
It's a severe inflammatory reaction.
重度の炎症反応です。
In fact, the inflammatory response is what we need, but chronic inflammation is not good
実際、炎症反応は私たちに必要なものですが、慢性的な炎症は良くありません
Then you just watched that Coli, I was thinking why people in the future can’t copy it
それからあなたはそのコリを見ました、私はなぜ未来の人々がそれをコピーできないのか考えていました
Because there's no way we're going to allow a hospital to feel so inflammatory.
病院がこれほど炎症を起こすことを許すわけがないからです。
Antibiotics knocked him out in the morning, because infection with inflammatory bacteria is serious
炎症性細菌による感染が深刻なため、抗生物質の投与により彼は朝倒れてしまいました
You were fast then, and...
あの時は君は速かった、そして…
So immediacy is gone
だから即時性がなくなった
Therefore, the current medical treatment cannot allow this kind of
したがって、現在の医療ではこのようなことは許されません。
The presence of an immediate bacterial infection such as
次のような即時性細菌感染症の存在
that in the past
過去のこと
In Coly100s
Coly100sで
you have no choice
あなたは選択肢がありません
no antibiotics at all
抗生物質はまったくありません
so you don't go to therapy
だからあなたはセラピーに行かないでください
So some patients will get serious infections
したがって、一部の患者は非常に重篤な感染症を引き起こす可能性があります
So like in a severe infection
重篤な感染症の場合と同じように
localized inflammation
局所的な炎症
Some patients may survive
一部の患者は生き残る可能性がある
the cancer may be under control
癌は制御されているかもしれない
However, some patients may have bacterial infections
ただし、患者によっては細菌感染症を患っている場合があります。
cause fatal
致命的な原因となる
inflammatory reaction
炎症反応
Like chronic inflammation vs instant inflammation
慢性炎症と即時炎症のようなもの
It's a different concept
それは違う概念です
chronic inflammation such as obesity
肥満などの慢性炎症
is a chronic inflammation
慢性炎症です
rhinohepatitis virus infection
鼻肝炎ウイルス感染症
It causes chronic inflammation of the liver
肝臓の慢性炎症を引き起こす
chronic inflammation it will create this environment
慢性炎症はこの環境を作り出します
Let the death of this cell
この細胞を死なせましょう
Increased replication rate
レプリケーション速度の向上
In fact, it also increases its mutation rate
実際、それは突然変異率も増加させます
increase the chance of cancer cells
がん細胞の可能性を高める
So this one might be heavier
なのでこちらの方が重いかもしれません
Some are to help IC package generation
一部はICパッケージの生成に役立ちます
But the activation of young cells requires an inflammatory environment
しかし、若い細胞の活性化には炎症環境が必要です
This is certain
これは確かです
it's almost time
もうすぐです
our last question
私たちの最後の質問
The teacher asks a question
先生が質問する
Will total flow T cells have something to do with genetics?
トータルフローT細胞は遺伝と関係があるのでしょうか?
Let's say the parents already have cancer
両親がすでに癌を患っているとしましょう
Will the cultivation of his T cells be effective for his children?
彼のT細胞の培養は彼の子供たちに効果があるでしょうか?
that is
あれは
Thanks
ありがとう
T cells cannot interact with each other
T細胞は互いに相互作用できない
I just said that T cells can only use your own
T細胞は自分自身の細胞しか利用できないと言いました
Why?
なぜ？
Because we humans probably know about organ rejection
なぜなら、私たち人間はおそらく臓器拒絶反応について知っているからです。
when you want to pass on your organs
臓器を伝えたいとき
You have to match your tissue antigens first
まず組織抗原を一致させる必要があります
Finding Rarely Becomes Finding Just Right
検索が適切な検索になることはほとんどありません
Otherwise there will be twins
そうしないと双子が生まれるよ
His tissue antigens are the same
彼の組織抗原は同じです
you can pass
あなたは合格できます
same concept
同じコンセプト
That is to say, your T cells
つまり、T細胞は
And who is that exclusion?
そして、その除外者は誰ですか？
It's the T cells that are rejecting
拒否しているのはT細胞です
Because he went to meet a foreign
外国人に会いに行ったから
something he doesn't know
他不認識的東西
He repells you and kills you
彼はあなたを撃退し、あなたを殺します
So if you want to do TCL
TCLをやりたい場合は
unless your one
あなたのものでない限り
of these tissue antigens
これらの組織抗原の
ask you
お聞き
To give you TCL exactly the same
まったく同じTCLを提供するには
That's probably only possible with soft twins.
それはおそらくソフトツインでのみ可能です。
the parents
両親
Your mother can, but your parents'
あなたのお母さんはできますが、あなたの両親は
To you, you're half dad
あなたにとって、あなたは半分お父さんです
half mom, right?
半分お母さんですよね？
so you that
だからあなたはそれを
parents too
両親も
also not
またそうではありません
usually you just
通常、あなたはただ
Use your own TCL
独自の TCL を使用する
to manufacture
製作する
to be able to use it on oneself
自分自身にも使えるようになる
So when we talked about Cartysail just now
それで、先ほど Cartysail について話したとき
Or something like TIL
またはTILのようなもの
T cell infusion therapy
T細胞輸入療法
from the patient's blood
患者の血液から
extract his T cells
彼のT細胞を抽出する
a lot of cultivation
たくさんの栽培
and inject it back into the patient
そしてそれを患者に注入します
That is, if
つまり、もし
The same soft twins have a chance
同じソフトツインにもチャンスがある
Others have no chance, that's what it means
他人にはチャンスがない、それが意味するもの
should be if you say you want
あなたが欲しいと言ったらそうすべきです
must use other people's words
他人の言葉を使わなければならない
Now you can technically use your own TIL
技術的には独自の TIL を使用できるようになりました
But I think technical development is theoretically not impossible
でも技術開発は理論的には不可能ではないと思います
Because you only need to say that the card you use is T cell
使うカードがT細胞って言えばいいだけだから
Is it not showing these reasons
これらの理由が表示されないのでしょうか
These organizations just mentioned seem theoretically possible
今言及したこれらの組織は理論的には可能であるように思われます
So I know that there are also people who are working on the card T cell
それで、カードT細胞に取り組んでいる人々もいることを知っています
Hope to make a universal T cell
万能T細胞を作りたい
Only in this way can it be used more quickly in most patients
この方法でのみ、ほとんどの患者でより迅速に使用できるようになります。
But these are still in the research stage
しかし、これらはまだ研究段階にあります
ok i now our time is up
さて、もう時間切れです
i know there are many questions
たくさんの質問があることは承知しています
So maybe that Mr. Tao would like to stay a few minutes longer
それでタオさんはあと数分滞在したいのかもしれません
But I think we're officially here now
しかし、私たちは今、正式にここにいると思います
that's where the speech ends
そこでスピーチは終わります
I'll make one now
今から作ります
Teachers are next month's knowledge prize banquet
先生たちは来月の知識賞の宴会です
Is the director of Lin Ziyi's special evaluation researcher at the law firm
法律事務所のリン・ツィイー特別評価研究員の所長です
The director of the law firm will conduct atomic and molecular research at the campus of National Taiwan University
法律事務所の所長は国立台湾大学のキャンパスで原子分子の研究を行う予定です
Institute of Science Former Branch
科学研究所旧分室
All are welcome on September 26th
9月26日は皆さん大歓迎です
ok then thanks again
わかりました、それではまたよろしくお願いします
Professor Tao Minhua
陶敏華教授
static performance static performance
静的パフォーマンス 静的パフォーマンス